<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/16/2014 10:59:03 AM -->
<GameData>

	<!-- ************************Build Texts********************************************-->


	
	<Language_en_US>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_ARCOLOGY">
			<Text>Arcology</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_ARCOLOGY_TEXT">
			<Text>An arcology is a massive structure designed to be largely, if not fully, self-sustaining, providing a completely enclosed environment for a large number of citizens to work and live.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] if adjacent to a Coast. Cannot be built adjacent to another Arcology.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_ARCOLOGY_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City, and +2 [ICON_GOLD] if adjacent to a Coast. Cannot be built adjacent to another Arcology.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_ARCOLOGY">
			<Text>Build an Arcology</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_ARCOLOGY_HELP">
			<Text>Build an Arcology which increases the Food and Gold yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_ARCOLOGY_REC">
			<Text>It will increases the Food and Gold yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME">
			<Text>Hydroponics Dome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME_TEXT">
			<Text>Artificial methods of cultivating food have grown increasingly sophisticated over time. The advent of new technologies such as hydroponics and aeroponics means that crops can be cultivated in entirely artificial environments, and communities that would normally struggle to feed their citizens can now cultivate crops nearby without needing to import food from more fertile areas.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food if built adjacent to a source of Fresh Water.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food if built adjacent to a source of Fresh Water. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME">
			<Text>Build a Hydroponics Dome</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Hydroponics Dome which increases the Food and Production yields of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_HYDROPONICS_DOME_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Food and Production yields of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX">
			<Text>Industrial Complex</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX_TEXT">
			<Text>As technology has advanced, so has industry.  Increasingly large and complex collections of factories, assembly plants, foundries, and other such industrial buildings begin to appear, as industries are grouped together to help facilitate production and encourage economies of scale. While the Industrial Site isn't as fully effective as the Manufactory, it can still provide a significant boost to production.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX_HELP">
			<Text>This improvement provides 2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX">
			<Text>Build an Industrial Complex</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX_HELP">
			<Text>Build an Industrial Complex which increases the Production yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_INDUSTRIAL_COMPLEX_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Production yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HERC">
			<Text>High-Energy Research Centre</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HERC_TEXT">
			<Text>As science has advanced, so have the tools needed to probe deeper into the secrets of the universe. While a lot of research is still conducted on an academic and theoretical level, the tools required to explore the mysteries of quantum mechanics or astrophysics require specialized laboratories and research centres.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_HERC_HELP">
			<Text>This improvement provides 12 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science and 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_PRESERVE">
			<Text>Nature Preserve</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_PRESERVE_TEXT">
			<Text>Scientific advancement has given mankind an increasing number of tools with which to manipulate their environment, but this has also meant that pristine, natural environments have become increasingly scarce. Whether to preserve natural ecosystems, or to encourage an increasing ecotourism industry, more and more Nature Preserves are being set aside.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This improvement provides 2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_PRESERVE_HELP">
			<Text>This improvement provides 2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_PRESERVE">
			<Text>Build a Nature Preserve</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_PRESERVE_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Nature Preserve which increases the Culture and Gold yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_PRESERVE_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Culture and Gold yields of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_BIOWELL">
			<Text>Eco-Commune</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_BIOWELL_TEXT">
			<Text>With increasing awareness of the impact of urbanization upon the environment, there were numerous efforts to try and establish more environmentally friendly and sustainable communities. While these communities always remained somewhat small, particularly compared to the much denser arcologies that began to appear afterwards, they were self-sufficient, and their location in relatively unspoilt areas of the wilderness meant they had a certain appeal for ecotourists.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food, 1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if built on a tile with access to Fresh Water.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_BIOWELL_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food, 1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture if built on a tile with access to Fresh Water. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_BIOWELL">
			<Text>Build an Eco-Commune</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_BIOWELL_HELP">
			<Text>Build an Eco-Commune which increases the Food, Culture, and Gold yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_BIOWELL_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Food, Culture, and Gold yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENOCENTRE">
			<Text>Genocentre</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENOCENTRE_TEXT">
			<Text>While most experimentation in genetic manipulation and engineering took place in dedicated genemod and transgenics labs located in urban centres, the development of increasingly diverse biomanufacturing processes created an increasing need for centres dedicated to genetic experimentation and development located away from the controlled environments of the cities. Built in undeveloped areas, these genocentres studied the impact of genetically modified organisms within natural environments.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food, 2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City, +2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food if built on a source of [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep or [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat, and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] if built on a source of [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle or [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses. Cannot be built adjacent to another Genocentre.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENOCENTRE_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food, 2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City, +2 [ICON_GROWTH] Food if built on a source of [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep or [ICON_RES_WHEAT] Wheat, and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] if built on a source of [ICON_RES_COW] Cattle or [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses. Cannot be built adjacent to another Genocentre. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENOCENTRE">
			<Text>Build a Genocentre</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENOCENTRE_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Genocentre which increases the Food, Production, and Gold yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENOCENTRE_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Food, Production, and Gold yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_COMM_ARRAY">
			<Text>Communications Array</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_COMM_ARRAY_TEXT">
			<Text>A communications array is an installation dedicated to helping facilitate the exchange of information across an area.  It initially provides a small increase in Gold over the Trading Post, but depending on which technologies have been researched, may also provide additional Culture or Science.  However, the Comm Array cannot be built adjacent to each other, limiting the number that can be constructed.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. Cannot be built adjacent to another Communications Array.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_COMM_ARRAY_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. Cannot be built adjacent to another Communications Array. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_COMM_ARRAY">
			<Text>Build a Communications Array</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_COMM_ARRAY_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Communications Array which increases the Gold yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_COMM_ARRAY_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Gold yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENERATOR">
			<Text>Generator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENERATOR_TEXT">
			<Text>As more and more industries became automated, they placed an increasing demand for power on available power plants and generators. The most heavily industrialized and automated regions began to develop numerous supplemental generators to help provide power to industry.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built on a tile with access to Fresh Water.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_GENERATOR_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on. +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built on a tile with access to Fresh Water. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENERATOR">
			<Text>Build a Generator</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENERATOR_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Generator which increases the Gold and Production yield of the tile. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_GENERATOR_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Gold and Production yield of the tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_CORE">
			<Text>Support Node</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_CORE_TEXT">
			<Text>As military units became increasingly sophisticated, it also became increasingly difficult to help maintain their equipment in the field. This was particularly prevalent in militaries that utilized extensive cybernetics, which lead to the development of the Support Node. These modular facilities provided both strong defensive positions, as well as extensive repair facilities and workshops to help maintain technologically sophisticated equipment for units in the field.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and 2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production if built on a Hill. It also heals nearby units for 10 HP each turn. Cannot be built adjacent to another Support Node.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_CORE_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold and 2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production to the tile it's built on, with an additional +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if adjacent to a City and +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production if built on a Hill. It also heals nearby units for 10 HP each turn. Cannot be built adjacent to another Support Node. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_CORE">
			<Text>Build a Support Node</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_CORE_HELP">
			<Text>Build a Support Node which provides Gold and Production, and also heals nearby units for 10 HP each turn. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FW_CORE_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the Gold and Production yield of the tile, as well as healing nearby units each turn.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_FUNGAL_GROWTH">
			<Text>Fungal Growth</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_FUNGAL_GROWTH_TEXT">
			<Text>The most visible effect of the release of the Pholus Mutagen has been the mutation of plants into fungal growths. The unusual plant forms have been observed to developing neural-like structures that allow them to interpret sensory information from their environments, and even respond with toxins and biochemical attacks against those they consider hostile, making areas overrun by the fungus to be quite hazardous for those unprepared for them to traverse. However, the fungus itself also appears to be living in symbiosis with humans and animals affected by the mutagen, providing them with useful sustenance and other valuable materials such as pharmaceuticals.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FW_FUNGAL_GROWTH_HELP">
			<Text>This custom improvement provides 1 [ICON_GROWTH] Food, 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and 1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold to the tile it's built on. It also inflicts 10 HP damage on any units that end their turn on or adjacent to it. [NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Provides bonus yield adjacent city.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CHOOSE_ARCH_ARTIFACT_RESULT">
			<Text>Artifact will be placed in nearest Great Work of Art slot. Artifact provides +4 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism. Archaeologist will be consumed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CHOOSE_ARCH_ARTIFACT_RESULT">
			<Text>Ancient writing will be placed in nearest Great Work of Writing slot. Writing provides +4 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +2 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism. Archaeologist will be consumed.</Text>
		</Replace>
		
		
		
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_REMOVE_ICE">
			<Text>Break Ice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_REMOVE_ICE_HELP">
			<Text>Clear the Ice on this tile to allow other naval units to pass (Unfortunately due to the limitation of the game, it will NOT change the terrian [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Graphic[ENDCOLOR] until reloading the game). </Text>
		</Row>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SPECIALTERRAIN_MOUNTAINS_TEXT">
			<Text>Mountains are impassable, except to air units. They provide nothing to cities. However, after researching the Advanced Engineering, workers can quarry the mountain to transform the Mountain to a Hill and produce a Stone resource</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_TRADING_POST_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Trading Posts are outposts where hunters and trappers may sell their wares to civilians in exchange for food, weapons, whiskey, gold, and all of the other trappings of society. They can generate a lot of wealth for a society.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][ICON_GOLD] Gold output and bonuses:
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold output for the tile.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if constructed near the coast or by the river (can mutiply to +2 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold).
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if constructed on the Road and +2 additional [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if constructed on the Railroad.
			</Text>
		</Replace>



		<!-- Science Improvement Change -->

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ACADEMY">
			<Text>Research Center</Text>
		</Replace>
		
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_ACADEMY_TEXT">
			<Text>A Research Center is a special facility located outside the city where scientists perform advanced or even secret research. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE] +8 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output for the tile. +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output if constructed near a mountain (can mutiply). </Text>
		</Replace>
		
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ACADEMY">
			<Text>Construct a Research Center</Text>
		</Replace>
		
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_GREAT_SCIENTIST_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Great Scientist can construct the special Research Center improvement which, when worked, produces lots of [ICON_RESEARCH] Science. Further, the Great Scientist lets you immediately learn any available technology. The Great Scientist is expended when used in any of both ways.</Text>
		</Replace>




		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_RAILROAD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A railroad is a set of rails - usually metal - upon which a vehicle runs. The earliest railed vehicles were carts pulled by animal power; the first steam-powered locomotive appeared in England at the end of the 18th century.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An unbroken chain of Railroads allows units to move extremely quickly through tiles (3 times faster than the road).
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After you researched the Railroad Technology, all Roads inside your territory will automatically upgrade to Railroads.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Railroad will NOT provide [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production bonus.
			</Text>
		</Replace>



		<!--************************New Improvements Texts*********************-->

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FISHERY_MOD">
			<Text>Fish Farming</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_FISHERY_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				In SuperPower Mod, the coast plot without any resources can also be improved by breeding a fish resource. It will provide additional [ICON_FOOD] Food output of the plot.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHERY_MOD">
			<Text>Create a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_FISHERY_MOD]Fish Resurce[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHERY_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				Breed a fish resource on costal tiles without resources. Then the worker will automatically build [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fishing Net[ENDCOLOR] to improve it and increase the city's [ICON_FOOD] Food output.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May only be constructed in a coastal tile without resources .
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed adjacent to another tile is currently under fish farming.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHERY_MOD_REC">
			<Text>In the Super Power Mod, you are allowed to build improvements on water tiles without resource increase the city's [ICON_FOOD]food output! </Text>
		</Row>


		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FISHING_BOATS">
			<Text>Workboats</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_FISHINGBOATS_TEXT">
			<Text>Workboats grant access to water-based luxury resources. Be aware that the "Worboats" is [COLOR_ADVISOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]DIFFERENT[ENDCOLOR] from "Fishing Boats" which grant access only to Fish Resources. Work Boats provide you with more Production and Gold bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHING_BOATS">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_FISHING_BOATS]WorkBoat[\LINK]</Text>
		</Replace>
		
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FISHFARM_MOD">
			<Text>Fishing Net</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_FISHFARM_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>Fishing Net grant access to Fish Resources (both natrual and man-made), improving the growth of nearby cities. Be aware that the "Fishing Net" is [COLOR_ADVISOR_HIGHLIGHT_TEXT]DIFFERENT[ENDCOLOR] from "Workboats" which grant access to water-based luxury resources.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHFARM_MOD">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_FISHFARM_MOD]Fishing Net[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHFARM_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>Fishing Net grant access to Fish Resources (both natrual and man-made), to improve it and increase the city's [ICON_FOOD] Food output. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed on a water-based luxury resource tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FISHFARM_MOD_REC">
			<Text>In the Super Power Mod, you are allowed to build improvements on water tiles without resource increase the city's [ICON_FOOD]Food output! </Text>
		</Row>
		

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_GAS_RIG_MOD">
			<Text>Natural Gas Drilling</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_GAS_RIG_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				In SuperPower Mod, the deep ocean without any resources can also be improved by digging out Natural Gas. It will provide additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production output of the plot.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_GAS_RIG_MOD">
			<Text>Drill a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_GAS_RIG_MOD]Natural Gas Resource[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_GAS_RIG_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				Drill out a natural  gas resource on ocean tiles without resources. Then the worker will automatically build an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Offshore Platform[ENDCOLOR] to improve it and increase the city's [ICON_PRODUCTION]Production output.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must be built on Ocean Tiles without resources.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed adjacent to another tile is currently under natural gas drilling.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_GAS_RIG_MOD_REC">
			<Text>In the Super Power Mod, you are allowed to build improvements on ocean tiles without resource to drill the natural gas!</Text>
		</Row>
		

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MOD">
			<Text>Pontoon Bridge</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MODE_HELP">
			<Text>The Pontoon Bridge allows land units to cross a single coastal tile without embarking.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Requires at least two adjacent land tiles. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed adjacent to another Pontoon Bridge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MOD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				A pontoon bridge or floating bridge or bridge of boats is a bridge that floats on water and in which barge- or boat-like pontoons support the bridge deck and its dynamic loads. While pontoon bridges are usually temporary structures, some are used for long periods of time. Permanent floating bridges are useful for sheltered water-crossings where it is not considered economically feasible to suspend a bridge from anchored piers. Such bridges can require a section that is elevated, or can be raised or removed, to allow ships to pass.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MOD">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_PONTOON_BRIDGE]Pontoon Bridge[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>Allows land units to cross a single coastal tile without embarking. May only be constructed in a coastal tile with 2 or more land tiles adjacent to it. May not be constructed adjacent to another Pontoon Bridge.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_PONTOON_BRIDGE_MOD_REC">
			<Text>It will allow land units to cross the Coastal tile.</Text>
		</Row>


		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_FORT">
			<Text>Naval Port</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_FORT_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The Naval Port allows any Naval Unit to enter the land tile where it is built. So it can be severed as a "canal" if built on the "Continental Bridge". May only be constructed on a Land Tile next to a Coast Tile.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] The Naval Unit inside the Naval Port will be vulnerable to enemy's Land Units attack.
			</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FORT">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_FORT]Naval Port[\LINK]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FORT_REC">
			<Text>It will allow naval units to cross this land tile.</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_FORT_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can only be built on [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Costal[ENDCOLOR] Land Tiles.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Allows [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Naval Units[ENDCOLOR] to enter this Tile so they can use it as a canal to go through isthmus.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Offer [ICON_STRENGTH] Defensive Bonus to the Land Units in this tile. But the naval unit will be [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]vulnerable [ENDCOLOR] to enemy Land Units' attack.</Text>
		</Replace>


		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CHATEAU">
			<Text>Winery</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_CHATEAU_TEXT">
			<Text>
				Portuguese wine is the result of traditions introduced to the region by ancient civilizations, such as the Phoenicians, Carthaginians, Greeks, and mostly the Romans. Portugal started to export its wines to Rome during the Roman Empire. Modern exports developed with trade to England after the Methuen Treaty in 1703. From this commerce a wide variety of wines started to be grown in Portugal. And, in 1758, one of the first wine-producing region of the world, the Região Demarcada do Douro was created under the orientation of Marquis of Pombal, in the Douro Valley. Portugal has two wine producing regions protected by UNESCO as World Heritage: the Douro Valley Wine Region (Douro Vinhateiro) and Pico Island Wine Region (Ilha do Pico Vinhateira). Portugal has a big variety of local kinds, producing a very wide variety of different wines with distinctive personality.
			</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHATEAU">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CHATEAU]Winery[\LINK]</Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHATEAU_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the amount of [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_GOLD] Gold provided by this tile. Receive bonus output if built on a Riverside or Coastal Tile. </Text>
		</Replace>
		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHATEAU_HELP">
			<Text>
				The Winery must be built adjacent to a luxury resource.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold if built on a Riverside or Coastal tile.
			</Text>
		</Replace>



		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_TERRACE_FARM_HELP">
			<Text>The Terrace Farm can only be built on hills and does not need a source of fresh water to do so. Each adjacent mountain will provides +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food and +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output for the Terrace Farm.</Text>
		</Replace>


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CREATE_FOREST_MOD">
			<Text>Forest Restoration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENTS_CREATE_FOREST_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				Plant trees on this tile to create a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Forest[ENDCOLOR]. This action can only be performed on Plains, Grassland or Tundra tiles.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Chopping down the newly planted Forest will also offer one-time Production. However comparing with the time you spent, it doesn't make sense.
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] Any previous features or improvements will be removed.
			</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CREATE_FOREST">
			<Text>Planting trees to create [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CREATE_FOREST_MOD]Forest[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CREATE_FOREST_HELP">
			<Text>
				Plant trees on this tile to create a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Forest[ENDCOLOR]. 
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must be built on Plains, Grassland or Tundra tiles without resources.
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] Any previous features or improvements will be removed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	
		


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CREATE_JUNGLE_MOD">
			<Text>Jungle Restoration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_CREATE_JUNGLE_MOD_HELP">
			<Text>
				Plant trees on this tile to create a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Jungle[ENDCOLOR]. This action can only be performed on Plains.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Chopping down the newly planted Jungle will also offer one-time Production. However comparing with the time you spent, it doesn't make sense.
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] Any previous features or improvements will be removed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CREATE_JUNGLE">
			<Text>Planting trees to create [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_CREATE_JUNGLE_MOD]Jungle[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CREATE_JUNGLE_HELP">
			<Text>
				Plant trees on this tile to create a [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Jungle[ENDCOLOR].
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must be built on Plains tiles without resources.
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] Any previous features or improvements will be removed.
			</Text>
		</Row>



		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_SHOSHONE_TIPI">
			<Text>Tipi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_SHOSHONE_TIPI_HELP">
			<Text>A Tipi can only be built on a Flat Terrain tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_SHOSHONE_TIPI_TEXT">
			<Text>The tipi (or teepee) is a portable, conical tent constructed of tanned hides and wooden poles traditionally associated with the migratory North American Plains Indians. The word itself comes from the Lakota for "they dwell." Often elaborately painted, tipis served to identify the separate tribes.</Text>
		</Row>
	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SHOSHONE_TIPI_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the amount of [ICON_FOOD] Food and [ICON_GOLD] Gold provided by this tile.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_SHOSHONE_TIPI">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_SHOSHONE_TIPI]Tipi[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>



		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE">
			<Text>Coffee/Cocoa Seedling</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE_HELP">
			<Text>
				You can seed coffee on a to generate a [ICON_RES_COFFEE] Coffee Resource on a Flat Grassland tile, or a [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa Resource on a Flat Plain tile.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Must be built on Flat Plains or Grasslands without resources.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed adjacent to another tile is currently seeding coffee/cocoa.
				[NEWLINE][COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]Warning:[ENDCOLOR] Any previous features or improvements will be removed.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE_TEXT">
			<Text>Coffee production in Ethiopia is a longstanding tradition. Ethiopia is where Coffea arabica, the coffee plant, originates. The plant is now grown in various parts of the world; Ethiopia itself accounts for around 3% of the global coffee market. </Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE_REC">
			<Text>It will create a [ICON_RES_COFFEE] Coffee or [ICON_RES_COCOA] Cocoa Resource on the tile</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE">
			<Text>Seeding [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ETHIOPIA_COFFEE]Coffee/Cocoa[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>


		
		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO">
			<Text>Byzantine Fort</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can be built on any tiles without resources.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Provides +50% defense bonus for units fighting on the tile.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Gain bonus yields (+2 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture, +2 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, +2 [ICON_PEACE] Faith) if built on Coastal Tiles.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO_TEXT">
			<Text>Angelokastro is a Byzantine castle on the island of Corfu, Greece. It is located at the top of the highest peak of the island's shoreline in the northwest coast near Palaiokastritsa and built on particularly precipitous and rocky terrain. </Text>
		</Row>

		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO_REC">
			<Text>It will pro</Text>
		</Row>-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO">
			<Text>Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_BYZANTIUM_ANGELOKASTRO]Byzantine Fort[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>



		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM">
			<Text>Forest Farming</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM_HELP">
			<Text>The Iroquoian people can build a farming inside a Forest without removing the forest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM_TEXT">
			<Text>The Iroquois are a mix of horticulturalists, farmers, fishers, gatherers and hunters, though their main diet traditionally has come from farming.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the amount of [ICON_FOOD] Food by this tile without removing the forest.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM">
			<Text>Begin [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_IROQUOIAN_FOREST_FARM]Forest Farming[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_ASSYRIA_FORT">
			<Text>Underground Fortress</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENT_ASSYRIA_FORT_HELP">
			<Text>
				+25% Combat Strength for your units when fighting within 2 hexes of the Underground Fortress and adjacent enemy units suffers -25 HP per turn.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]An Underground Fortresscan be built outside your border or even inside other nation's borders. However two Underground Fortress cannot be built next to each other.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENT_ASSYRIA_FORT_TEXT">
			<Text>Underground bunkers are among the world's most fascinating structures.</Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_ASSYRIA_FORT">
			<Text>
				Construct a [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_ASSYRIA_FORT]Underground Fortress[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>


		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MAYA_ALTAR">
			<Text>Altar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENT_MAYA_ALTAR_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can only be built in Jungle or Forest.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE] Each adjacent mountain will provides +1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science output for the Altar.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENT_MAYA_ALTAR_TEXT">
			<Text>An altar is any structure upon which offerings such as sacrifices and worship are made for religious purposes. Altars are usually found at shrines, and they can be located in temples, churches and other places of worship. </Text>
		</Row>

		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MAYA_ALTAR_REC">
			<Text>It will increase the amount of [ICON_RESEARCH] Science by this tile without removing the features.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_MAYA_ALTAR">
			<Text>Construct an [LINK=IMPROVEMENT_MAYA_ALTAR]Altar[\LINK]</Text>
		</Row>






		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_IMPROVEMENT_MOUNTAIN_ROCKS">
			<Text>Mountain Quarrying</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_MOUNTAIN_ROCKS_HELP">
			<Text>
				Can only be built on Mountain plots. This order will transform the Mountain to Hill and a Stone resource will appear on the hill.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]May not be constructed adjacent to another tile is currently.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE](Unfortunately due to the limitation of the game, it will NOT change the terrian [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Graphic[ENDCOLOR] until reloading the game).
			</Text>
		</Row>
		

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CITADEL_HELP">
			<Text>A [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fixed Citadel Unit[ENDCOLOR] is created after finishing building the Citadal. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In the late game, the Citadal can serve as an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Airfield[ENDCOLOR] to deploy Land-based Aircraft and Nuclear Weapons. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Citadal costs a certain amount of [ICON_GOLD] Maintenance Cost (but NO [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower Cost) accroding to its Fixed Citadal Unit.</Text>
		</Replace>

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_CITADEL_TEXT">
			<Text>
				In SuperPower Mod, the Citadel is very different from its original design. It can be built either by militia units (need a long building time) or by great generals (built instantly). A [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Fixed Citadel Unit[ENDCOLOR] is created after finishing building the Citadal. The Fixed Citadel Unit can provide sight and attack enemy units within 1 hex range on your command. In the late game, the Citadal can serve as an [COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Airfield[ENDCOLOR] to deploy Land-based Aircraft and Nuclear Weapons.
				[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Citadal costs a certain amount of [ICON_GOLD] Maintenance Cost (but NO [ICON_RES_MANPOWER] Manpower Cost) accroding to its Fixed Citadal Unit.immediately.</Text>
		</Replace>
		
		
		<!--<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_CHATEAU_REC">
			<Text>A Chateau must be built adjacent to a Luxury resource.  [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It will increase the Culture and Gold yield of the tile. Also provides a defensive bonus.</Text>
		</Replace>-->


		<!--<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_IMPROVEMENTS_FEITORIA_HELP">
			<Text>A Feitoria can only be built in a City-State's lands. It can only be built on a land tile  with no resource. It provides to you one copy of each Luxury Resource type that City-State has connected, regardless of your status with that City-State, but that copy cannot be traded. It also provides the same +50% defense bonus as a Fort. Can only be built by the Portuguese.</Text>
		</Replace>-->

		<Replace Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILD_KASBAH_HELP">
			<Text>
				Constructs a Kasbah, which will grant +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food, [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production, and [ICON_GOLD] Gold provided by this tile.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if built on a Riverside or Coastal tile.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+1 [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if built on Roads. +2 [ICON_GOLD] Gold output if built on Railroads.
				[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]+50% defensive bonus for units fighting on the tile.</Text>
		</Replace>
		
	</Language_en_US>
	
	
	
	

</GameData>