<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/7/2015 11:47:36 PM -->
<GameData>
		<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3SEPOY">
			<Text>Sepoy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3SEPOY_HELP">
			<Text>Gunpowder unit that excels at city combat. Only India may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3SEPOY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sepoy is an Indian unique unit. Unlike the Musketman it replaces, it has a combat bonus against cities and earns more experience from combat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3SEPOY_TEXT">
			<Text>A Sepoy (from Persian "sipahi" meaning "soldier"), in its most common application, was the term used in the British Indian Army for an infantry private. The Mughal Emperor Aurangzeb raised battalions of sepoys variously armed with matchlocks, rockets, and grenades. These troops were successfully employed in siege warfare, particularly during the Siege of Bidar, the Siege of Bijapur and the Siege of Golconda.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term sepoy came into use in the forces of the British East India Company in the eighteenth century, where it was one of many, such as peons, gentoos, mestees and topasses used for various categories of native soldiers. Initially it referred to Hindu or Muslim soldiers without regular uniform or discipline. It later generically referred to all native soldiers in the service of the European powers in India. Close to ninety-six percent of the British East India Company's army of 300,000 men were native to India and these sepoys played a crucial role in securing the subcontinent for the company.</Text>
		</Row>
			<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3SEPOY">
				<Text>Rebel</Text>
			</Row>
			<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3SEPOY_HELP">
				<Text>Earns more experience from combat (50%).</Text>
			</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_FLAG</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>flag_sepoy.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3SEPOY256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3SEPOY128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>3SEPOY80.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3SEPOY64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3SEPOY_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3SEPOY45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>