<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/07/17 1:35:50 PM -->
<GameData>
	<UnitClasses>
		<Row>
			<Type>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</Description>
			<DefaultUnit>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</DefaultUnit>-->			
			<MaxPlayerInstances>5</MaxPlayerInstances>
		</Row>
	</UnitClasses>
	<Units>
		<Row>
			<Class>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</Class>
			<Type>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</Type>
			<PrereqTech>TECH_RADAR</PrereqTech>
			<ObsoleteTech>TECH_ROBOTICS</ObsoleteTech>
			<Combat>100</Combat>
			<Moves>5</Moves>
			<Cost>700</Cost>			
			<!--<FaithCost>300</FaithCost>
			<RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>true</RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>-->
			<CombatClass>UNITCOMBAT_NAVALMELEE</CombatClass>
			<Domain>DOMAIN_SEA</Domain>
			<DefaultUnitAI>UNITAI_ATTACK_SEA</DefaultUnitAI>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_HELP</Help>
			
			<PurchaseOnly>true</PurchaseOnly>
			<MoveAfterPurchase>true</MoveAfterPurchase>
			<MilitarySupport>true</MilitarySupport>
			<MilitaryProduction>true</MilitaryProduction>
			
			<Pillage>true</Pillage>

			<Mechanized>true</Mechanized>			
			<AdvancedStartCost>200</AdvancedStartCost>
			<MinAreaSize>10</MinAreaSize>
			<XPValueAttack>3</XPValueAttack>
			<XPValueDefense>3</XPValueDefense>
			<UnitArtInfo>ART_DEF_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitArtInfo>			
			<IconAtlas>UNIT_ATLAS_2</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>20</PortraitIndex>
			<UnitFlagAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_FLAG_ATLAS</UnitFlagAtlas>
			<UnitFlagIconOffset>46</UnitFlagIconOffset>
			<MoveRate>BOAT</MoveRate>
			<ExtraMaintenanceCost>80</ExtraMaintenanceCost>
		</Row>
	</Units>

	<Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_SMAN_EU_NAVAL_YARD</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>

	<Unit_AITypes>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_ATTACK_SEA</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_RESERVE_SEA</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_ESCORT_SEA</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_EXPLORE_SEA</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_AITypes>

	<Unit_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>18</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_NAVAL_RECON</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>4</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Unit_Flavors>

	<Unit_FreePromotions>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_SEE_INVISIBLE_SUBMARINE</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_ANTI_SUBMARINE_II</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_WITHDRAW_BEFORE_MELEE</PromotionType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_FreePromotions>
	
	<UnitGameplay2DScripts>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER</UnitType>
			<SelectionSound>AS2D_SELECT_BATTLESHIP</SelectionSound>
			<FirstSelectionSound>AS2D_BIRTH_BATTLESHIP</FirstSelectionSound>
		</Row>
	</UnitGameplay2DScripts>


	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER">
			<Text>[ICON_IDEOLOGY_AUTOCRACY] Submarine Hunter</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_HELP">
			<Text>Powerful Atomic Era Mercenary naval melee unit which specializes in anti-submarine warfare. Price shown is how much it costs to hire this unit for 20 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				Use the Submarine Hunter to send your enemy's fleet to the bottom of the briny deep.				
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_SMAN_SUB_HUNTER_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				The Submarine Hunter is an Atomic era Mercenary naval melee unit, available upon the discovery of Radar. The Naval Yard is required for this unit to be built. The Submarine Hunter becomes obsolete upon the discovery of Robotics.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Sub Hunters are small, fast, and cheap ships specifically designed to find and destroy enemy submarines, using a discipline of combat known as Anti-Submarine Warfare, or ASW.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first attacks on a ship by an underwater vehicle are generally believed to have been during the American Revolutionary War, using what would now be called a naval mine but what then was called a torpedo, though various attempts to build submarines had been made before this. The first self-propelled torpedo was invented in 1863 and launched from surface craft. The first submarine with a torpedo was Nordenfelt I built in 1884-1885, though it had been proposed earlier. In the Russo-Japanese War of 1904-05, the submarine was a significant threat. By the start of the First World War nearly 300 submarines were in service. Some warships were fitted with an armored belt as protection against torpedoes.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]During the First World War, submarines were a major menace. They operated in the Baltic, North Sea, Black Sea and Mediterranean as well as the North Atlantic. Previously they had been limited to relatively calm and protected waters. The vessels used to combat them were a range of small, fast surface ships using guns and good luck. They mainly relied on the fact a submarine of the day was often on the surface for a range of reasons, such as charging batteries or crossing long distances. The first approach to protect warships was chain link nets strung from the sides of battleships, as defense against torpedoes. Nets were also deployed across the mouth of a harbor or naval base to stop submarines entering or to stop torpedoes of the Whitehead type fired against ships. British warships were fitted with a ram with which to sink submarines, and U-15 was thus sunk in August 1914.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The first recorded sinking of a submarine by depth charge was U-68, sunk by Q-ship HMS Farnborough off Kerry, Ireland 22 March 1916. By early 1917, the Royal Navy had also developed indicator loops which consisted of long lengths of cables lain on the seabed to detect the magnetic field of submarines as they passed overhead. At this stage they were used in conjunction with controlled mines which could be detonated from a shore station once a 'swing' had been detected on the indicator loop galvanometer. Indicator loops used with controlled mining were known as 'guard loops'. By July 1917, depth charges had developed to the extent that settings of between 50–200 ft were possible. This design would remain mainly unchanged through the end of World War II. While dipping hydrophones appeared before war's end, the trials were abandoned. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Seaplanes and airships were also used to patrol for submarines. A number of successful attacks were made, but the main value of air patrols was in driving the U-boat to submerge, rendering it virtually blind and immobile.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]However, the most effective anti-submarine measure was the introduction of escorted convoys, which reduced the loss of ships entering the German's War Zone around the British Isles from 25% to less than 1%.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>	
  
</GameData>