<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by Tomatekh -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA">
			<Text>Sofa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_HELP">
			<Text>Skirmisher Unit excelling at hit-and-run tactics and supporting your army. Only Songhai may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Sofa is a Songhai unique unit, replacing the Crossbowman. As a Ranged unit, it can deal significant damage to other Medieval Era units up to two hexes away, but is vulnerable to melee attack. It serves as an excellent support unit starting with the Medic I promotion and the ability to move after firing on the enemy. The Sofa has a slightly higher defensive strength, but is weaker at ranged combat.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_SOFA_TEXT">
			<Text>Sofa is a Mandinka term for slave soldiers who served in the army of the Mali Empire. Sofas were recruited from "jonow" (slaves) captured in battle or bought from afar. They could be depended on in most instances for obedience, since their livelihood depended entirely on their master. The institution of slavery in the Mali Empire heavily rewarded loyalty, and jonow could rise to civil or military positions of prominence. Jonow became part of their master's clan, and were often freed after a certain amount of years. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]In the forest and swampy areas of the Mali Empire, cavalry was minimized or altogether abandoned making sofas the exclusive instrument of war. Sofas were equipped with two quivers, and their bow was small by European standards. It could not fire very far or even powerfully, so sofas utilized deadly poisons and fired in arcs to give the arrows strength.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>UNIT_ALPHA_SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>MaliUnitAlphaAtlas.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>

		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon080.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon064.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>SOFA_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>SofaIcon045.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>