<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 3/9/2015 7:16:50 PM -->
<GameData>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMBOOT_GUILD">
			<Text>Isicathulo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMBOOT_GUILD_TEXT">
			<Text>
				The gumboot dance (Isicathulo) is an African dance that is performed by dancers wearing wellington boots, also called gumboots. The boots were a solution to a problem of often flooded gold mines in which men otherwise stood in knee-deep water toiling at their work stations. Gumboot dancing was conceived by black miners in South Africa as an alternative to drumming—which authorities restricted. Another reason for gumboot dancing was for the miners in South Africa as they worked they sang. It is also thought that the workers used the gumboots to relay messages to each other that they did not want their bosses to overhear.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]  Gumboot dancing started to spread outside of the gold mines and into the communities as a form of entertainment. As the dance became popular, the employers took the dancers and formed troupes to represent their company. They had the troupes perform to visitors and spread the good word about their company, but most of the performances were done in the workers own language. This allowed the dancers to express how they really felt by mocking their employers to their face and them not even knowing it. These performances lead to popularizing this style of dance to where it is performed worldwide today.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMBOOT_GUILD_HELP">
			<Text>[ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness-enhancing building that yields additional [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production from minable resources. Only the Zulus may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_GUMBOOT_GUILD_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Isicathulo is a Zulu unique construction that increases the [ICON_HAPPINESS_1] Happiness of a city. Unlike the Circus it replaces, minable resources in the city yield an additional 1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production. It is available upon the discovery of Mining.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>


	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>GUMBOOT_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>GUMBOOT256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>GUMBOOT_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>GUMBOOT128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>GUMBOOT_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>GUMBOOT64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>GUMBOOT_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>GUMBOOT45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>