<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>

	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANYA">
			<Text>[ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Banya</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANYA_HELP">
			<Text>+25% [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great People generation in the city. +1 [ICON_FOOD] Food from every Tundra and Snow tile worked by this City. Culture growth of borders costs 25% less. Only Russia may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANYA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Like the standard Garden, the Russian Banya increases the rate of [ICON_GREAT_PEOPLE] Great Person generation in the City. However, it also provides [ICON_FOOD] Food for each Tundra and Snow tile worked, doesn't require fresh water, and costs no maintenance. The Banya reduces the culture cost to grow a city's borders, letting Russia rapidly expand into and use colder lands.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_BANYA_TEXT">
			<Text>Banya is a small room or building designed as a place to experience dry or wet heat sessions, or an establishment with one or more of these facilities. The steam and high heat make the bathers perspire. In the Russian language, the word "banya" may also refer to public bathhouse. The original bathhouses were detached, low-lying wooden structures dependent on a fire lit inside to provide heat. A stove in a corner is made of large round stones that, when heated, are lifted with iron rods and placed in a wooden tub. Once the fire is built, the bather then removes the fire and flushes out the smoke before beginning the bath.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Banya buildings can be quite large with a number of different bathing areas or simple wooden cabins like the traditional Finnish cottage saunas. Russian banyas usually have three rooms: a steam room, a washing room and an entrance room. The entrance room, called a predbannik or pre-bath, has pegs to hang clothing upon and benches to rest on. The washing room has a hot water tap, which uses water heated by the steam room stove and a vessel or tap for cold water to mix water of a comfortable temperature for washing. The heater has three compartments: a fire box that is fed from the entrance room, the rock chamber, which has a small hole to throw the water into and a water tank at the top. The top of the water tank is usually closed to prevent vapour from infiltrating the banya. Water from a bucket by the stove is poured over the heated rocks in the stove. There are wooden benches across the room. People enter the steam room when the stove is hot, but before water is poured on the rocks. Getting a good sweat is thought to protect and condition the skin from the steam.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>
