<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_DOLMEN">
			<Text>[ICON_PRODUCTION] Dolmen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_DOLMEN_HELP">
			<Text>Increases the [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production of a city. +1 [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture from all sources of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble and [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone worked by this City. Only the French may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_DOLMEN_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Dolmen is the French unique replacement for the Stone Works. In addition to yielding [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and improving the yield of [ICON_RES_MARBLE] Marble and [ICON_RES_STONE] Stone, the Dolmen also yields [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and can be built in any City. The Dolmen has no technology prerequisite, so it can be built right away.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_DOLMEN_TEXT">
			<Text>A dolmen is a type of single-chamber megalithic tomb, usually consisting of two or more vertical megaliths supporting a large flat horizontal capstone ("table"), although there are also more complex variants. Most date from the early Neolithic (4000–3000 BC). Dolmens were typically covered with earth or smaller stones to form a tumulus. In many instances, that covering has weathered away, leaving only the stone "skeleton" of the burial mound intact.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]It remains unclear when, why, and by whom the earliest dolmens were made. The oldest known dolmens are in Western Europe, where they were set in place around 7,000 years ago. The Carnac stones are an exceptionally dense collection of megalithic sites around the village of Carnac, in Brittany, consisting of alignments, dolmens, tumuli and single menhirs. More than 3,000 prehistoric standing stones were hewn from local rock and erected by the pre/proto-Celtic people of Brittany, and are the largest such collection in the world.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]There are several dolmens scattered around the area. These dolmens are generally considered to have been tombs; however, the acidic soil of Brittany has eroded away the bones. They were constructed with several large stones supporting a capstone, then buried under a mound of earth. In many cases, the mound is no longer present, sometimes due to archeological excavation, and only the large stones remain, in various states of ruin.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

</GameData>