<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 8/6/2013 1:15:40 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_RUSHER">
			<Text>Rusher</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_RUSHER_HELP">
			<Text>Gunpowder units that is not slowed by rough terrain and excels at urban combat. Only the Iroquois may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_RUSHER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Rusher is an Iroquois unique unit. Although it is weaker than the Musketman it replaces, the Rusher suffers no movement penalty in rough terrain and receives an attack boost when attacking cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3UC_RUSHER_TEXT">
			<Text>
				During the seventeenth century the Iroquois, unlike many other tribes, had easy access to trade goods at Dutch posts along the Hudson River. Weapons of war, such as the iron axe and musket, were highly sought items, and by the 1640s the Iroquois were well equipped with these goods and used them against their enemies. Historical descriptions of Iroquois assaults against fortified villages were first reported in the 1640s. At this time the Iroquois effectively invaded Huronia and began attacking and successfully destroying Huron villages.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Attacks on fortified positions involved the use of direct assaults, which are defined as attempts to penetrate the outer defensive walls of a village or fortified position by a large number of warriors attacking one or several points along its front, likely focused on what was thought to be the weakest part of an enemy's defense. Once an outer wall was reached, warriors fired through existing loopholes or gaps into the interior of a village, while others attempted to chop down the outer palisades at the base. In this task the iron hatchet was a crucial element in Iroquois assaults, as it allowed users the ability to quickly hack down walls. Once a wall was breached, warriors rushed inside to kill or capture the defenders.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3UC_RUSHER">
			<Text>Swift Movement</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3UC_RUSHER_HELP">
			<Text>Ignores terrain costs (lost upon upgrade).</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>UNIT_ALPHA_PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>rusher.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>prowler_256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>prowler_128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>prowler_80.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>prowler_64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>PROWLER_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>prowler_45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>

</GameData>