<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by Tomatekh -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<!-- Ahmadi -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1AHMADI">
			<Text>Go on Hajj to the Holy City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCAHMADI">
			<Text>Going on a pilgrimage is one of the pillars of Islam, and this is something every able bodied Muslim is expected to do once in his life.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Akatt-u -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1AKATTU">
			<Text>Perform a Purification Ritual</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCAKATTU">
			<Text>The sacred waters of the five rivers can purify us and make us ready to perform sacrifice. Let us cleanse our bodies so that we may honor the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Al-Asnam -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ASNAM">
			<Text>Honour the Exalted Cranes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCASNAM">
			<Text>We shhould carve idols and pray for the blessing of Al-Lat, Al-Uzza, and Al-Manat; the exalted goddesses whose intercession is hoped for.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Amanaiism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1AMANAIISM">
			<Text>Sleep in the Royal Tombs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCAMANAIISM">
			<Text>By sleeping on the tombs of our ancestors, they may visit us in our dreams and impart prophecy to aid our kingdom and community.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Angakkuqism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ANGAKKUQISM">
			<Text>Go on a Great Hunt </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCANGAKKUQISM">
			<Text>The angakkuq has returned from the world of the spirits and Sedna has promised to make the oceans plentiful. Let us embark on a great hunt to bring food and comfort to our people, and afterwards let us give thanks to the whale spirit for allowing us the hunt.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Anito -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ANITO">
			<Text>Celebrate the Kadayawan Festival</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCANITO">
			<Text>The Kadaywan is a weeklong celebration of the harvest, in which we come together as a community to give thanks to Bathala. Let us prepare for the festivities as our citizens dress in costume to sing and dance and set up arenas to watch the horse fights.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Anglicanism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ANGLICANISM">
			<Text>Write a Confession of Faith</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCANGLICANISM">
			<Text>Our churches have a long history of composing Confessions of Faith; formal declarations of belief. Though many serve as theses for debate, others seek unity between groups on controversial doctrines. Let us draft our own Confession in an effort to formalize doctrinal standards.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Arianism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ARIANISM">
			<Text>Appoint Church Leaders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCARIANISM">
			<Text>The church lacks men to lead it. We are in a position to correct this. Let us aid the church in seeking out wise and godly men to appoint as the leaders of Arianism![NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Atanodjuwaja -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ATANODJUWAJA">
			<Text>Construct Horns of Consecration</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCATANODJUWAJA">
			<Text>Let us construct an altar modeled from the horns of sacrificial oxen so that we may honor the gods and give libation.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Atenism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ATENISM">
			<Text>Celebrate a Royal Jubilee</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCATENISM">
			<Text>Great Pharaoh, the time has come to hold a royal jubilee and renew your divine right of kingship. Let us race the Apis bull and offer sacrifice to Aten.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Ashurism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ASHURISM">
			<Text>Celebrate the Akitu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCASHURISM">
			<Text>A new half year has begun and your subjects are already preparing a festival to celebrate the sowing of the barley. Let us move the statue of Ashur from the great house and honour his victory of Tiamat, renewing our great city and asking Ashur's blessings for the coming year.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Bahai -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1BAHAI">
			<Text>Perform the Nineteen Day Fast</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCBAHAI">
			<Text>The Nineteen Day Fast was instituted by Bahá'u'lláh. Bringing together the community, it represents a period of meditation and prayer during which the believer must strive to make the necessary readjustments in his inner life and to refresh and reinvigorate his soul.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Baptist -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1BAPTIST">
			<Text>Appoint Church Leaders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCBAPTIST">
			<Text>The church lacks men to lead it. We are in a position to correct this. Let us aid the church in seeking out wise and godly men to appoint as the leaders of Christianity![NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Bird Figure -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1BIRD_FIGURE">
			<Text>Perform a Fertility Rite</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCBIRD_FIGURE">
			<Text>We mold the woman into the shape of a bird, the shape of a snake, the shape of a frog. Just as the woman gives birth to the wheat and the quince, we ask the woman to give birth to a son.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Bogomils -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1BOGOMILISM">
			<Text>Elect Teachers</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCBOGOMILISM">
			<Text>St. Paul taught us that simpleminded men should instruct one another. Therefore, we pray in private houses and elect teachers from amongst our congregation to be our spiritual guides.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Bumuntu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1BUMUNTU">
			<Text>Perform Lubuko</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCBUMUNTU">
			<Text>Only through divining the will of our ancestors can we hope to avoid misfortune. Let the nsengha drink mwavi and enter the realm of dreams in order to learn the will of the bankambo.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Cathars -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1CATHARISM">
			<Text>Appoint Church Leaders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCCATHARISM">
			<Text>The church lacks men to lead it. We are in a position to correct this. Let us aid the church in seeking out wise and godly men to appoint as the leaders of the Cathars![NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Chiminagua -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1CHIMINAGUA">
			<Text>Perform the El Dorado Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCCHIMINAGUA">
			<Text>You must renew your kingship and be recognized by the tribal chiefs! Come, be anointed in gold as you journey to the great lagoon and make votive offerings to the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Druze -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1DRUZE">
			<Text>Celebrate the Ziyarat al-Nabi Shu'ayb</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCDRUZE">
			<Text>Let us make a pilgrimage to the shrine of the Prophet Shu'ayb. Shu'ayb is the chief prophet of the Druze religion to whom God passed on his revelation directly before passing it on to Moses.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Fat Roog -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1FAT_ROOG">
			<Text>Hold the Raan Festival</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCFAT_ROOG">
			<Text>After the first new moon, we prepare the sacred shrines and holy places and make offerings of millet and milk to our ancestors.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Hermeticism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1HERMETICISM">
			<Text>Perform a Theurgic Ritual</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCHERMETICISM">
			<Text>By performing the ritual acts and identifying the divine sumbolon, the vehicle of our souls can align with the divine hierarchy and theurgic union can be achieved.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Heros Karabazmos -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1HEROS_KARABAZMOS">
			<Text>Create a Hand of Sabazios</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCHEROS_KARABAZMOS">
			<Text>A Hand of Sabazios is a bronze ritual hand used to adorn altars and carried during religious processions. On its palm and fingers we cast details of our rider god, Sabazios, and his great hunt.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>	
		<!-- Hussites -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1HUSSITISM">
			<Text>Appoint Church Leaders</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCHUSSITISM">
			<Text>The church lacks men to lead it. We are in a position to correct this. Let us aid the church in seeking out wise and godly men to appoint as the leaders of the Hussites![NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Imperial Cult -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1IMPERIAL_CULT">
			<Text>Pronounce Apotheosis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCIMPERIAL_CULT">
			<Text>Your honorable father has passed! Let the senate vote and elevate him to the rank of god so that we may better our lineage and strengthen imperial authority.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>				
		<!-- Intiism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1INTIISM">
			<Text>Celebrate the Inti Raymi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCINTIISM">
			<Text>The winter solstice is fast approaching and already your subjects have begun to organize dances and processions for the festival. We should prepare sacrifice for Inti and Pachamama to ensure a good harvest in the coming season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Jain -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1JAIN">
			<Text>Celebrate the Mahavir Jayanti</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCJAIN">
			<Text>Mahavir Jayanti is our most important holiday. During the festival we celebrate the birth of Mahavira; the twenty fourth and last Tirthankara. Let us prepare the rath yatra and carry the image of Mahavira through our cities on a chariot.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Kachina -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1KACHINA">
			<Text>Create a Kachina Doll</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCKACHINA">
			<Text>Our people strive for a closer connection to their ancestors. Let us create a vessel for the spirits, to protect us and provide good fortune in the coming season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Laiboni -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1LAIBONI">
			<Text>Perform a Cattle Sacrifice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCLAIBONI">
			<Text>Ngai has blessed us with rain and the grass has grown tall to feed our cattle! Let the laiboni offer sacrifice to give thanks and honor Ngai's gift.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Mahoma -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MAHOMA">
			<Text>Hold the Autumn Festival</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMAHOMA">
			<Text>Our subjects eagerly await the Autumn Festival. Let us don our animal masks and lead a procession to the mound temple so that we may offer sacrifice to the three gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mandaenism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MANDEANISM">
			<Text>Baptize the Faithful</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMANDEANISM">
			<Text>Baptism helps cleanse the material evil of the body, redeeming our soul and bringing it closer to salvation.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mani -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MANICHAEISM">
			<Text>Commemorate the Prophet</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMANICHAEISM">
			<Text>The prophet Mani offered us a vision of spiritual light of the world overcoming material darkness. We take a day to remember him and commemorate his birth as we read Manichaean scripture.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Midewiwin -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MIDEWIWIN">
			<Text>Hold the Midwinter Festival</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMIDEWIWIN">
			<Text>The first new moon of the year symbolizes a time to give thanks to the spirits and renew our connection with nature. Let us stir the ashes of our hearths and have the midew cleanse the village before holding a great feast in honour of Nanabozho.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mithras -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MITHRAISM">
			<Text>Construct a Mithraeum</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMITHRAISM">
			<Text>A great cave lies in the mountains to our east. We should convert it into the image of the universe so that we may initiate others into the mysteries and hold our cultic meal.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mysteries -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MYSTERIES">
			<Text>Call the Gathering</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMYSTERIES">
			<Text>Let the hierophants declare prorrhesis and perform sacrifice, as the initiates hold their night vigil and drink barley and kykeon.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mormonism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MORMONISM">
			<Text>Celebrate Pioneer Day</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMORMONISM">
			<Text>On this day we celebrate our brothers and sisters who first settled these lands after being forced from their homes. Let us hold parades and other festivities to help commemorate the event.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Muism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MUISM">
			<Text>Perform a Bear Sacrifice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMUISM">
			<Text>The end of winter approaches. Let us capture a newborn bear cub so that we may send it off to the world of the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Mutazila -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MUTAZILA">
			<Text>Go on Hajj to the Holy City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMUTAZILA">
			<Text>Going on a pilgrimage is one of the pillars of Islam, and this is something every able bodied Muslim is expected to do once in his life.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Mwari -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MWARI">
			<Text>Perform a Kraal Sacrifice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMWARI">
			<Text>Our sangoma fear that the amadholozi have grown displeased with our actions. We should sacrifice cattle in the umsamo of our chief to help placate and honour our ancestors.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Napirtunis -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1NAPIRTUNIIS">
			<Text>Celebrate the Akitu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCNAPIRTUNIIS">
			<Text>A new half year has begun and your subjects are already preparing a festival to celebrate the sowing of the barley. Let us move the statue of Kiririsha from the great house to the sea, renewing our great city and asking Kiririsha's blessings for the coming year.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Neoplatonism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1NEOPLATONISM">
			<Text>Perform a Theurgic Ritual</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCNEOPLATONISM">
			<Text>By performing the ritual acts and identifying the divine sumbolon, the vehicle of our souls can align with the divine hierarchy and theurgic union can be achieved.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Num -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1NUM">
			<Text>Perform a Healing Dance</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCNUM">
			<Text>Tell the healers to prepare the night dance to aid our community. Let them tie the offerings to the trees and bang their drums to contact the spirits of our ancestors.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Numenism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1NUMENISM">
			<Text>Perform Haruspicy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCNUMENISM">
			<Text>Let us sacrifice a newborn sheep and examine its liver for omens so that we may better discern the will of the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Odinani -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ODINANI">
			<Text>Create an Ikenga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCODINANI">
			<Text>Our people strive for a closer connection to their ancestors. Let us create a vessel for the spirits, to protect us and provide good fortune in the coming season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Onyamesom -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ONYAMESOM">
			<Text>Hold the Yam Festival</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCONYAMESOM">
			<Text>The Yam Festival is a five day feast marking the first yam harvest following the monsoon season. It is a time for us to thank Nyame and the spirits of our ancestors as we come together in peace and community.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Pajelanca -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1PAJELANCA">
			<Text>Collect Medicinal Herbs</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCPAJELANCA">
			<Text>A sickness is spreading through our empire and the paje inform us that a malevolent spirit is attacking the souls of the poor. We need to collect a new supply of sacred herbs so that the paje may enter the spirit world and combat this evil.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Puta Tupuna -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1PUTA_TUPUNA">
			<Text>Celebrate Makahiki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCPUTA_TUPUNA">
			<Text>The Makahiki season has arrived and our warriors put down their spears to celebrate the new year. Let our priests offer ho'okupu to Lono, as our people feast and wrestle to prove their strength.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Tangata Manu -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1TANGATA_MANU">
			<Text>Celebrate Makahiki</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCTANGATA_MANU">
			<Text>The Makahiki season has arrived and our warriors put down their spears to celebrate the new year. Let our priests offer ho'okupu to Lono, as our people feast and wrestle to prove their strength.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Razana -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1RAZANA">
			<Text>Perform the Turning of the Bones</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCRAZANA">
			<Text>The spirits of the dead only join the world of the ancestors after their bodies fully decompose. We must observe the famadihana tradition and exhume our ancestors so that we may rewrap them in fresh cloth. By marking the occasion with song and dance we bring together the spirits of the living and the dead and grow as a community.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Romuva -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ROMUVA">
			<Text>Hold a Rozhanitsy Meal </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCROMUVA">
			<Text>At the end of year we invoke the great god Rod to honor mothers and midwives and ensure the birth of strong sons in the following season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sairimaism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SAIRIMAISM">
			<Text>Hold a Kurgan Burial</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSAIRIMAISM">
			<Text>A great hero has died! Let us build a great barrow and fill his burial chamber with gold as we sacrifice a horse to honor his spirit.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Saman -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SAMAN">
			<Text>Perform a Bear Sacrifice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSAMAN">
			<Text>The end of winter approaches. Let us capture a newborn bear cub so that we may send it off to the world of the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Santeria -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SANTERIA">
			<Text>Obtain the Elekes</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSANTERIA">
			<Text>In order to be initiated into the faith, we must receive the protection and blessing of the Orichas. We must receive the colored beads of Elegua, Obatala, Yemaya, Chango, and Ochun and fasten a necklace to be bathed in blood.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Satsana Phi -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SATSANA_PHI">
			<Text>Conduct a Baci Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSATSANA_PHI">
			<Text>Through the Baci we synchronize the thirty-two components of the soul. By observing the ritual we can establish social and familial bonds to maintain the balance and harmony of the individual and community.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Sgaanaang -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SGAANAANG">
			<Text>Carve a Transformation Mask</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSGAANAANG">
			<Text>Masks play an important role in our religious ceremonies; displaying the crest of our ancestors and their relationship with the spirits of nature. When we wear the mask with song and dance, we transform into the animal spirit and call upon our ancestors for help and guidance.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Shiva -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SHIVA">
			<Text>Perform a Lingam Offering</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSHIVA">
			<Text>The lingam represents the great Shiva. Let us prepare the lingam as well as the yoni of his consort and pour offerings of milk and ghee.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Siskur-mes -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SISKURMES">
			<Text>Celebrate the Akitu</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSISKURMES">
			<Text>A new half year has begun and your subjects are already preparing a festival to celebrate the sowing of the barley. Let us move the statute of Anu from the great house and honour his victory of Nammu, renewing our great city and asking Anu's blessings for the coming year.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Slavianism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SLAVIANISM">
			<Text>Hold a Rozhanitsy Meal</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSLAVIANISM">
			<Text>At the end of year we invoke the great god Rod to honor mothers and midwives and ensure the birth of strong sons in the following season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Southern Cult -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1SOUTHERN_CULT">
			<Text>Hold the Green Corn Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCSOUTHERN_CULT">
			<Text>The time of the summer harvest is fast approaching. As our priests prepare to sacrifice the first of the green corn to give thanks and ensure the yearly crop, let us catch game and rehearse the feather dance so that our people may celebrate the coming season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Patagonia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1TEMAUKELISM">
			<Text>Hold a Hain Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCTEMAUKELISM">
			<Text>Our children have become men and it is time to initiate them into the traditions and secrets of our people. Let them paint their bodies and train in the ways of the spirits as we hold a hain ceremony to mark the occasion.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Tjukurpa -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1TJUKURPA">
			<Text>Hold an Initiation Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCTJUKURPA">
			<Text>A few of our youth have reached the aged of manhood. Let the elders take them into the bush and teach them the sacred songs and dances of the dreaming before they are painted with white ochre and circumcised so that they may be accepted as warriors.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Tzolkin -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1TZOLKIN">
			<Text>Hold the Festival of Chicckaban</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCTZOLKIN">
			<Text>During the month of Xul we hold a festival dedicated to the great Feathered Serpent. Let us burn incense and bring offerings to the temples so that Kulkulcan may descend from the heavens and collect his sacrifice.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Vedic -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1VEDIC">
			<Text>Perform a Fire Sacrifice</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCVEDIC">
			<Text>The sacrifice is an act of cosmic renewal. Through Agni, the sacrificial fire, we destroy an object in the world of man so that we may renew that object in the world of the gods.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Voodoo -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1VODUN">
			<Text>Draw a Veve</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCVODUN">
			<Text>Great Houngan, we must prepare for the coming ritual. Let us draw the veve on the floor with red brick powder so that the Loas may descend to earth.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Yazdansim -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1YAZDANISM">
			<Text>Hold the Feast of the Assembly</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCYAZDANISM">
			<Text>Once a year we hold a seven day festival to reaffirm our community and sense of identity. During this time, all able bodied Yazidi should endeavor to make a pilgrimage to the tomb of Sheikh Adi ibn Musafir in Lalis where we sacrifice an ox to mark the end of summer.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<!-- Zemiism -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ZEMIISM">
			<Text>Create a Zemi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCZEMIISM">
			<Text>Our people strive for a closer connection to their ancestors. Let us create a vessel for the spirits, to protect us and provide good fortune in the coming season.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Malagan -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1MALAGAN">
			<Text>Hold a Malanggan Ceremony</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCMALAGAN">
			<Text>The Malanggan is a ceremony where we come together as a village to honour our dead by repaying our debts and obligations to one another. Let us carve totems and masks for the recently departed; burning these icons or leaving them in caves to ensure a good hunt and harvest.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Micronesia -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1ITANG">
			<Text>Perform the Kampa Ritual</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_DECISIONS_RELIGIONEVENTS_1_DESCITANG">
			<Text>Rak, the season of plenty, is upon us and it is time to reaffirm our dedication to the gods and spirits of this land. Let us put away the yams and taro and offer breadfruit so that we may find favor and ensure that our nets will always be bountiful.[NEWLINE]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Esotericism Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM">
			<Text>Esotericism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_ISLAM">
			<Text>Sufism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_JUDAISM">
			<Text>Kabbalah</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_CHRISTIAN">
			<Text>Apophatic Theology</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_EASTERN">
			<Text>Hesychasm</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_GREEK">
			<Text>Orphism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_TAOISM">
			<Text>Neidan</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_ITAN">
			<Text>Ifá</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_HINDU">
			<Text>Yoga</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NORSE">
			<Text>Seidhr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_SIOUX">
			<Text>Medicine Society</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_AFRICA">
			<Text>Muti</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_CONFUCIAN">
			<Text>Xinxue</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_PROTESTANT">
			<Text>Pentecostalism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NEW_AGE">
			<Text>New Age Movement</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_DESC">
			<Text>A new mystic tradition has begun to develop among our religious elite. Adopting some of these ideas into mainstream belief would likely give us a greater understanding of our faith, but may also make it more inaccessible to outsiders.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_PROTESTANT_DESC">
			<Text>An interdenominational renewal movement has begun to take hold in our church. Encouraging this development may spark a new found enthusiasm in our faith, but may also decrease the unity of our greater communion.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NEW_AGE_DESC">
			<Text>A New Age religious movement has emerged in our cities. Promoting its message of universal peace and love could increase our popularity among youth groups, but would likely be met with opposition by established church leaders.</Text>
		</Row>		
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Let us explore the secrets of our faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_PROTESTANT_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Let us celebrate our personal connection to the Holy Spirit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NEW_AGE_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>Let us enter the Age of Aquarius!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Your Cities will produce 20% less Religious Pressure[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith for every 5 [ICON_CITIZEN] Citizens in your Cities[ENDCOLOR]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>These ideas are dangerous to the uninitiated!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_PROTESTANT_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>This movement doesn't interest us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NEW_AGE_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>They're just a bunch of hippies...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith per City[ENDCOLOR]
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_OUTCOME_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A new mystic tradition has emerged!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_PROTESTANT_OUTCOME_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>A renewal movement has spread through our church!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ESOTERICISM_NEW_AGE_OUTCOME_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>The Age of Aquarius has begun!</Text>
		</Row>		
		<!-- Spiritualism Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_SPIRITUALISM">
			<Text>Spiritualism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_SPIRITUALISM_DESC">
			<Text>A growing interest in the spirit world has taken hold in your cities as your educated elite attempt to use emerging sciences to prove the existence of an afterlife.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_SPIRITUALISM_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>The spirits will guide us!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_SPIRITUALISM_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Religious Buildings will also provide +2 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_SPIRITUALISM_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Your citizens are attempting to contact the spirit world!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Rosicrucian Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS">
			<Text>Rosicrucian Enlightenment</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_DESC">
			<Text>Anonymous manifestos have begun to circulate among the educated elite of your cities declaring the existence of a secret brotherhood of alchemists and sages who are preparing to transform religion, the arts and sciences, and the political landscape. While tales of the mysterious Christian Rosenkreuz and his fabled Chemical Wedding are confusing much of your populace, others see it as a call to arms to form an Invisible College and further the emerging sciences.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>The manifestos are an allegory of our faith.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain [ICON_PEACE] Faith equal to the amount of [ICON_PEACE] Faith needed to spawn your next Great Prophet ({1_Award} [ICON_PEACE] Faith)[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_2">
			<Text>The manifestos are a model for emerging sciences.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_2_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Gain [ICON_RESEARCH] Science equal to half the amount of [ICON_PEACE] Faith needed to spawn your next Great Prophet ({1_Award} [ICON_RESEARCH] Science)[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>			
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Rosicrucianism has provided your citizens with new insights into their faith!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ROSY_CROSS_OUTCOME_2_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Rosicrucianism has inspired your citizens to form an Invisible College!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Revelation Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_REVELATION">
			<Text>Revelation</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_REVELATION_DESC">
			<Text>While observing your kingdom a great light appears to break through the clouds before slowly moving in the direction of a nearby mountain. None of your advisors can claim to have witnessed the event, but you are convinced it held some meaning.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_REVELATION_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>This must be a sign from the heavens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_REVELATION_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]+{1_Award} [ICON_PEACE] Faith[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_REVELATION_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>You have received a message from the heavens!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Atheism Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ATHEISM">
			<Text>Atheism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ATHEISM_DESC">
			<Text>Advances in science and technology have led many of your citizens to question religious truths and even the existence of God.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ATHEISM_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>This is a sign of the times...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ATHEISM_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Your Cities will randomly lose religious followers[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_ATHEISM_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Your citizens have begun to question the existence of God!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Rapture Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_RAPTURE">
			<Text>The Rapture</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_RAPTURE_DESC">
			<Text>Citizens all across your empire have mysteriously vanished leaving nothing behind but their clothes. The scientific community is baffled while religious leaders are claiming that the missing population ascended into heaven.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_RAPTURE_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>I guess we were left behind...</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_RAPTURE_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lose 1 to 3 [ICON_CITIZEN] Population in all Cities[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_RAPTURE_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Citizens across your empire have mysteriously vanished!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Millenarianism Event -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_DOOM_CULT">
			<Text>Millenarianism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_DOOM_CULT_DESC">
			<Text>The approaching millennium has caused a minor panic among your citizens, many of whom are convinced the world is going to end.</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_DOOM_CULT_OUTCOME_1">
			<Text>They must be joking... right?</Text>
		</Row>	
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_DOOM_CULT_OUTCOME_1_DESC">
			<Text>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]50% chance to suffer [ICON_RESISTANCE] Anarchy after you reach the year AD {1_Date}[ENDCOLOR][NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET][COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]50% chance to enter a minor [ICON_GOLDEN_AGE] Golden Age after you reach the year AD {1_Date}[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_EVENT_TOMATEKH_HR_DOOM_CULT_OUTCOME_1_NOTIFICATION">
			<Text>Your citizens are convinced the world is going to end!</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Dummy -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY">
			<Text>HR Dummy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_TEXT">
			<Text>HR Dummy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_PEACE] Faith per City</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_DESC">
			<Text>HR Dummy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_HELP">
			<Text>Cities produce 25% less Religious Pressure.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_STRATEGY">
			<Text>This building cannot be constructed.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVLOPEDIA_HR_ESOTERIC_DUMMY_TEXT">
			<Text>Esotericism refers to a wide array of ideas and movements which have developed within Western society, and which have remained largely distinct from both orthodox Judeo-Christian religion and Enlightenment rationalism. A trans-disciplinary field, esotericism has pervaded various forms of Western philosophy, religion, pseudoscience, art, literature, and music, continuing to have an impact on intellectual ideas and popular culture.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_SPIRITUALIST_DUMMY">
			<Text>HR Dummy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_SPIRITUALIST_DUMMY_TEXT">
			<Text>HR Dummy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_POLICY_HR_SPIRITUALIST_DUMMY_HELP">
			<Text>+1 [ICON_RESEARCH] Science from Religious Buildings</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>