<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/08/17 7:00:36 AM -->
<GameData>
	
	<UnitClasses>
		<Row>
			<Type>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</Description>
			<DefaultUnit>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</DefaultUnit>
			<MaxPlayerInstances>5</MaxPlayerInstances>
		</Row>
	</UnitClasses>
	<Units>
		<Row>
			<Class>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</Class>
			<Type>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</Type>
			<Combat>10</Combat>
			<RangedCombat>15</RangedCombat>
			<Range>2</Range>
			<Moves>3</Moves>
			<Cost>60</Cost>
			<!--<FaithCost>240</FaithCost>
			<RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>true</RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>-->
			<PrereqTech>TECH_ANIMAL_HUSBANDRY</PrereqTech>
			<ObsoleteTech>TECH_CIVIL_SERVICE</ObsoleteTech>
			<CombatClass>UNITCOMBAT_MOUNTED</CombatClass>
			<Domain>DOMAIN_LAND</Domain>
			<DefaultUnitAI>UNITAI_RANGED</DefaultUnitAI>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_HELP</Help>
			
			<PurchaseOnly>true</PurchaseOnly>
			<MoveAfterPurchase>true</MoveAfterPurchase>
			<MilitarySupport>true</MilitarySupport>
			<MilitaryProduction>true</MilitaryProduction>
			<NoMaintenance>true</NoMaintenance>
			<Pillage>true</Pillage>

			<AdvancedStartCost>100</AdvancedStartCost>
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<XPValueAttack>3</XPValueAttack>
			<XPValueDefense>3</XPValueDefense>
			<UnitArtInfo>ART_DEF_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitArtInfo>
			<IconAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>56</PortraitIndex>
			<UnitFlagAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_FLAG_ATLAS</UnitFlagAtlas>
			<UnitFlagIconOffset>56</UnitFlagIconOffset>
			<MoveRate>QUADRUPED</MoveRate>
			<ExtraMaintenanceCost>40</ExtraMaintenanceCost>
		</Row>
	</Units>

	<!--
	
	
	<Unit_ResourceQuantityRequirements>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<ResourceType>RESOURCE_HORSE</ResourceType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_ResourceQuantityRequirements>
	-->

	<Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_SMAN_EU_MERC_GUILD</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>

	<Unit_AITypes>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_RANGED</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_DEFENSE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_FAST_ATTACK</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_AITypes>

	<Unit_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>7</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_RANGED</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>12</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_MOBILE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>14</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Unit_Flavors>

	<Unit_FreePromotions>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_HITANDRUN</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_CAN_MOVE_AFTER_ATTACKING</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_ONLY_DEFENSIVE</PromotionType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_FreePromotions>

	<Unit_ClassUpgrades>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<UnitClassType>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_FRANKISH_CROSSBOWMAN</UnitClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_ClassUpgrades>

	<UnitGameplay2DScripts>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER</UnitType>
			<SelectionSound>AS2D_SELECT_CAVALRY</SelectionSound>
			<FirstSelectionSound>AS2D_BIRTH_CAVALRY</FirstSelectionSound>
		</Row>
	</UnitGameplay2DScripts>


	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER">
			<Text>[ICON_IDEOLOGY_AUTOCRACY] Horse Bowman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_HELP">
			<Text>Fast Ancient Era ranged mounted unit.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Use the Akkadian Horse Bowman to strike your enemies from afar. They may move after attacking, but receive no defensive bonus from terrain.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_AKKADIAN_HORSE_ARCHER_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				The Akkadian Horse Bowman is an Ancient era ranged mounted unit, available upon the discovery of Animal Husbandry. The Akkadian Horse Bowman becomes obsolete upon the discovery of Civil Service, at which time it may upgrade to the Frankish Mounted Crossbowman unit.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				Mounted archery first developed during the Iron Age, gradually replacing the Bronze Age chariot. The earliest depictions of mounted archers are found in artwork of the Neo-Assyrian Empire of about the 9th century BC and reflects the incursions of the early Iranian peoples. Early horse archery, depicted on the Assyrian carvings, involved two riders, one controlling both horses while the second shot.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Skirmishing requires vast areas of free space to run, maneuver and flee, and if the terrain is close, light horse archers can be charged and defeated easily. Light horse archers are also very vulnerable to foot archers and crossbowmen, who are smaller targets and can outshoot horsemen. Large armies very seldom relied solely on skirmishing mounted archers, but there are many examples of victories in which horse archers played a leading part. The Roman general Crassus led a large army, with inadequate cavalry and missile troops, to catastrophe against Parthian horse archers and cataphracts at the Battle of Carrhae. The Persian king Darius the Great led a campaign against the mounted Scythians, who refused to engage in pitched battle; Darius conquered and occupied land but lost enough troops and supplies that he was compelled to retreat. Darius, however, kept the lands he had conquered.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]According to the Greek historian Herodotus, the Persian general Mardonius used horse archers to attack and harass his opponents during the Battle of Plataea, which was won by the Greeks. Philip of Macedon scored an epic victory against the Scythians residing north of the Danube, killing their king, Ateas, and causing their kingdom to fall apart thereafter. Alexander the Great defeated Scythians, Sakas in 329 BC at the Battle of Jaxartes, at the Syr Darya river. Later on, Alexander himself used mounted archers recruited among the Scythians and Dahae, during the Greek invasion of India.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Roman Empire and its military also had an extensive use of horse archers after their conflict with eastern armies that relied heavily on mounted archery in the 1st century BC. They had regiments such as the Equites Sagittarii, who acted as Rome's mounted horse archers in combat. The Crusaders used conscripted cavalry and horse archers known as the Turcopole, made up of mostly Greek and Turks.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Heavy horse archers first appeared in the Assyrian army in the 7th century BC after abandoning chariot warfare and formed a link between light skirmishing cavalrymen and heavy cataphract cavalry. The heavy horse archers usually had mail or lamellar armor and helmets, and sometimes even their horses were armored. Heavy horse archers, instead of skirmishing and hit-and-run tactics, formed in disciplined formations and units, sometimes intermixed with lancers as in Byzantine and Turkish armies, and shot as volleys instead of shooting as individuals. The usual tactic was to first shoot five or six volleys at the enemy to weaken him and to disorganize them, and then charge. Heavy horse archers often carried spears or lances for close combat, or formed mixed units with lancers. The Mongol armies and others included both heavy and light horse archers.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

</GameData>