<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 10/27/2010 4:15:53 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3OROMO">
			<Text>Oromo Warrior</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3OROMO_TEXT">
			<Text>The Oromo are a cultural group that has lived for centuries in the area today known as Ethiopia. Historically defined by their unique democratic caste system, each age group within the Oromo was assigned to a specific position within society. As an Oromo citizen aged, they progressed through these age groupings to assume different positions within the Oromo hierarchy. Young men between the ages of sixteen and thirty-two were traditionally assigned to the warrior caste. Young Oromo men were not fully considered men until they had killed a man or, in times of peace, a fierce animal.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Bravery in combat was paramount among Oromo culture, and many of their customs required retelling the histories of great warriors. These storytelling traditions reinforced the warlike attitude prevalent throughout Oromo society. In addition to this focus on military achievement, the Oromo also heavily stressed the importance of harmony and peace amongst their people. This unifying ideal ensured that if any outside military force attacked an Oromo tribe, they could expect a united Oromo counterattack.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3OROMO_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Oromo Warrior is an Ethiopian unique unit. Unlike the Musketman it replaces, it has the Shock I and Shock II promotions, allowing it to fight much better in open terrain.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_3OROMO_HELP">
			<Text>Early gunpowder unit that fights best on flat terrain. Only Ethiopia may build it.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3OROMO">
			<Text>Rite of Passage</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_3OROMO_HELP">
			<Text>Earns extra experience from combat.</Text>
		</Row>-->
	</Language_en_US>
	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>oromo_256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>oromo_128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>80</IconSize>
			<Filename>oromo_80.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>oromo_64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>oromo_45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3OROMO_FLAG</Atlas>
			<IconSize>32</IconSize>
			<Filename>IconOromo32.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>

</GameData>
