<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/08/17 7:00:36 AM -->
<GameData>
	
	<UnitClasses>
		<Row>
			<Type>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</Description>
			<DefaultUnit>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</DefaultUnit>
			<MaxPlayerInstances>5</MaxPlayerInstances>
		</Row>
	</UnitClasses>
	<Units>
		<Row>
			<Class>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</Class>
			<Type>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</Type>
			<Combat>75</Combat>
			<Moves>3</Moves>
			<Cost>500</Cost>
			<!--<FaithCost>600</FaithCost>
			<RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>true</RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>-->
			<PrereqTech>TECH_MASS_MEDIA</PrereqTech>
			<ObsoleteTech>TECH_NANOMATERIALS</ObsoleteTech>
			<CombatClass>UNITCOMBAT_MELEE</CombatClass>
			<Domain>DOMAIN_LAND</Domain>
			<DefaultUnitAI>UNITAI_ATTACK</DefaultUnitAI>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_HELP</Help>

			
			<PurchaseOnly>true</PurchaseOnly>
			<MoveAfterPurchase>true</MoveAfterPurchase>
			<MilitarySupport>true</MilitarySupport>
			<MilitaryProduction>true</MilitaryProduction>
			
			<Pillage>true</Pillage>

			<AdvancedStartCost>160</AdvancedStartCost>
			
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<XPValueAttack>3</XPValueAttack>
			<XPValueDefense>3</XPValueDefense>
			<UnitArtInfo>ART_DEF_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitArtInfo>
			<IconAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>43</PortraitIndex>
			<UnitFlagAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_FLAG_ATLAS</UnitFlagAtlas>
			<UnitFlagIconOffset>35</UnitFlagIconOffset>
			<MoveRate>BIPED</MoveRate>
			<ExtraMaintenanceCost>180</ExtraMaintenanceCost>
		</Row>
	</Units>

	<Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_SMAN_EU_MERC_CONSULATE</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>

	<Unit_AITypes>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_ATTACK</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_DEFENSE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_EXPLORE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_AITypes>

	<Unit_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>24</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>16</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Unit_Flavors>

	<Unit_FreePromotions>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_PROMOTION</PromotionType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_FreePromotions>

	<UnitGameplay2DScripts>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA</UnitType>
			<SelectionSound>AS2D_SELECT_INFANTRY</SelectionSound>
			<FirstSelectionSound>AS2D_BIRTH_INFANTRY</FirstSelectionSound>
		</Row>
	</UnitGameplay2DScripts>


	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA">
			<Text>[ICON_IDEOLOGY_AUTOCRACY] Task Force 141(Disavowed)</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_HELP">
			<Text>Modern Era Mercenary melee unit. Price shown is how much it costs to hire this unit for 20 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_STRATEGY">
			<Text>
				The Guerrilla unit excels at non traditional military operations. It may move after attacking, receive a +15 combat bonus in friendly territory, pillage at no movement cost, and have a 25% chance of withdrawing from combat. It receives no defensive terrain bonuses and -50% combat strength when attacking cities.
			</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_GUERILLA_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				The Guerrilla is a Modern era Mercenary melee unit, available upon the discovery of Plastics. The Mercenary Consulate is required for this unit to be built. The Guerrilla becomes obsolete upon the discovery of Nanotechnology.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The term, the diminutive form of 'war' in Spanish, is usually translated as 'little war,' and the word, guerrilla, has been used to refer to the concept as early as the 18th century. In correct Spanish usage, a person who is a member of a guerrilla unit is a guerrillero if male, or a guerrillera if female. This term became popular during the early-19th century Peninsular War, when the Spanish people rose against the Napoleonic troops and fought against a highly superior army using the guerrilla strategy.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The term 'guerrilla' was used in English as early as 1809 to refer to the fighters, e.g. 'The town was taken by the guerrillas', and also, as in Spanish, to denote a group or band of such fighters. However, in most languages guerrilla still denotes the specific style of warfare. The use of the diminutive evokes the differences in number, scale, and scope between the guerrilla army and the formal, professional army of the state.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]The Chinese general and strategist Sun Tzu, in his 'The Art of War' in the 6th century BCE, was the earliest to propose the use of guerrilla warfare. This directly inspired the development of modern guerrilla warfare. Guerrilla tactics were presumably[original research?] employed by prehistoric tribal warriors against enemy tribes. Evidence of conventional warfare, on the other hand, did not emerge until 3100 BC in Egypt and Mesopotamia. Since the Enlightenment, ideologies such as nationalism, liberalism, socialism, and religious fundamentalism have played an important role in shaping insurgencies and guerrilla warfare. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]One of the most remarkable guerrilla warfare warriors was Viriatus, a Lusitanian who led the resistance against the Roman Empire by obtaining several victories between 147 BC and 139 BC in the region of Zamora, Spain. Because of the innovative tactics he used during his command, he made himself the name of Terror Romanorum , or Terror of the Romans.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

</GameData>