<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 12/08/17 7:00:36 AM -->
<GameData>
	
	<UnitClasses>
		<Row>
			<Type>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</Type>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</Description>
			<DefaultUnit>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</DefaultUnit>
			<MaxPlayerInstances>3</MaxPlayerInstances>
		</Row>
	</UnitClasses>
	<Units>
		<Row>
			<Class>UNITCLASS_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</Class>
			<Type>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</Type>
			<Combat>60</Combat>
			<Moves>4</Moves>
			<Cost>250</Cost>
			<!--<FaithCost>240</FaithCost>
			<RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>true</RequiresFaithPurchaseEnabled>-->
			<PrereqTech>TECH_GUNPOWDER</PrereqTech>
			<ObsoleteTech>TECH_DYNAMITE</ObsoleteTech>
			<CombatClass>UNITCOMBAT_MOUNTED</CombatClass>
			<Domain>DOMAIN_LAND</Domain>
			<DefaultUnitAI>UNITAI_FAST_ATTACK</DefaultUnitAI>
			<Description>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</Description>
			<Civilopedia>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_PEDIA</Civilopedia>
			<Strategy>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_STRATEGY</Strategy>
			<Help>TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_HELP</Help>

			
			<PurchaseOnly>true</PurchaseOnly>
			<MoveAfterPurchase>true</MoveAfterPurchase>
			<MilitarySupport>true</MilitarySupport>
			<MilitaryProduction>true</MilitaryProduction>
			
			<Pillage>true</Pillage>

			<AdvancedStartCost>30</AdvancedStartCost>
			
			<MinAreaSize>-1</MinAreaSize>
			<XPValueAttack>3</XPValueAttack>
			<XPValueDefense>3</XPValueDefense>
			<UnitArtInfo>ART_DEF_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitArtInfo>
			<IconAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_ATLAS</IconAtlas>
			<PortraitIndex>36</PortraitIndex>
			<UnitFlagAtlas>SMAN_EXOTIC_UNIT_FLAG_ATLAS</UnitFlagAtlas>
			<UnitFlagIconOffset>28</UnitFlagIconOffset>
			<MoveRate>QUADRUPED</MoveRate>
			<ExtraMaintenanceCost>45</ExtraMaintenanceCost>
		</Row>
	</Units>

	<Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<BuildingClassType>BUILDINGCLASS_SMAN_EU_MERC_GUILD</BuildingClassType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_BuildingClassRequireds>

	<Unit_AITypes>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_FAST_ATTACK</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<UnitAIType>UNITAI_DEFENSE</UnitAIType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_AITypes>

	<Unit_Flavors>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_OFFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>9</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_DEFENSE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>3</Flavor>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<FlavorType>FLAVOR_MOBILE</FlavorType>
			<Flavor>5</Flavor>
		</Row>
	</Unit_Flavors>

	<Unit_FreePromotions>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_NO_DEFENSIVE_BONUSES</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_CAN_MOVE_AFTER_ATTACKING</PromotionType>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<PromotionType>PROMOTION_CITY_PENALTY</PromotionType>
		</Row>
	</Unit_FreePromotions>
	
	<UnitGameplay2DScripts>
		<Row>
			<UnitType>UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER</UnitType>
			<SelectionSound>AS2D_SELECT_KNIGHT</SelectionSound>
			<FirstSelectionSound>AS2D_BIRTH_KNIGHT</FirstSelectionSound>
		</Row>
	</UnitGameplay2DScripts>


	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER">
			<Text>[ICON_IDEOLOGY_AUTOCRACY] Cavalier</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_HELP">
			<Text>Fast Renaissance Era mounted Mercenary melee unit. Price shown is how much it costs to hire this unit for 20 turns.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Use the Cavalier to quickly route and scatter your enemies. They may move after attacking, but receive no defensive bonus from terrain and a penalty when attacking cities.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_EXOTIC_UNIT_CAVALIER_PEDIA">
			<Text>
				The Cavalier is a Renaissance era Mercenary mounted melee unit, available upon the discovery of Gunpowder. The Mercenary Guild is required for this unit to be built. The Cavalier becomes obsolete upon the discovery of Dynamite.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]
				The term Cavalier was first used by Roundheads as a term of abuse for the wealthier Royalist supporters of King Charles I and his son Charles II of England during the English Civil War, the Interregnum, and the Restoration, from 1642 to 1679. It was later adopted by the Royalists themselves. Although it referred originally to political and social attitudes and behavior, of which clothing was a very small part, it has subsequently become strongly identified with the fashionable clothing of the court at the time. Prince Rupert, commander of much of Charles I's cavalry, is often considered to be an archetypal Cavalier.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cavalier derives from the same Latin root as the French word chevalier, as well as the Spanish word caballero, the Vulgar Latin word caballarius, meaning 'horseman.' Shakespeare used the word cavaleros to describe an overbearing swashbuckler or swaggering gallant in Henry IV, Part 2, in which Shallow says 'I'll drink to Master Bardolph, and to all the cavaleros about London.'[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Cavalier was not understood at the time as primarily a term describing a style of dress, but a whole political and social attitude. However, in modern times the word has become more particularly associated with the court fashions of the period, which included long flowing hair in ringlets, brightly colored clothing with elaborate trimmings and lace collars and cuffs, and plumed hats. This contrasted with the dress of at least the most extreme Roundhead supporters of Parliament, with their preference for shorter hair and plainer dress, although neither side conformed to the stereotypical images entirely.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Most Parliamentarian generals wore their hair at much the same length as their Royalist counterparts, though Cromwell was something of an exception. The best patrons in the nobility of Charles I's court painter Sir Anthony van Dyck, the archetypal recorder of the Cavalier image, all took the Parliamentary side in the Civil War. Probably the most famous image identified as of a 'cavalier,' Frans Hals' Laughing Cavalier, shows a gentleman from the strongly Calvinist Dutch town of Haarlem, and is dated 1624. These derogatory terms, for at the time they were so intended, also showed what the typical Parliamentarian thought of the Royalist side: capricious men who cared more for vanity than the nation at large.
			</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

</GameData>