<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 8/5/2013 2:12:16 PM -->
<GameData>
	
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_RANCH">
			<Text>[ICON_PRODUCTION] Ranch</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_RANCH_HELP">
			<Text>Increases a city's [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production and increases the rate of border growth. </Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_RANCH_STRATEGY">
			<Text>The Ranch is an American unique building that improves the [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production yield of [ICON_RES_COW] Cows, [ICON_RES_HORSE] Horses, [ICON_RES_DEER] Deer, [ICON_RES_BISON] Bison, and [ICON_RES_SHEEP] Sheep. +15% [ICON_PRODUCTION] Production when building mounted units. Unlike the Stable it replaces, it also greatly increases the rate of border growth and has no resource requirement.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_3UC_RANCH_TEXT">
			<Text>A ranch is a type of farm and an area of landscape given primarily to the practice of ranching, the practice of raising grazing livestock such as cattle or sheep for meat or wool. Ranching is also a method used to raise less common livestock such as elk, American bison or even ostrich, emu, and alpacas.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Ranches generally consist of large areas, but may be of nearly any size. If the ranch includes arable or irrigated land, the ranch may also engage in a limited amount of farming, raising crops for feeding the animals, such as hay and feed grains. As settlers from the United States moved west, they brought cattle breeds developed on the east coast and in Europe along with them, and adapted their management to the drier lands of the west by borrowing key elements of the Spanish vaquero culture.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>

	<IconTextureAtlases>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_RANCH_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>256</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_ranch256.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_RANCH_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>128</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_ranch128.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_RANCH_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>64</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_ranch64.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
		<Row>
			<Atlas>3UC_RANCH_ICON_ATLAS</Atlas>
			<IconSize>45</IconSize>
			<Filename>3uc_ranch45.dds</Filename>
			<IconsPerRow>1</IconsPerRow>
			<IconsPerColumn>1</IconsPerColumn>
		</Row>
	</IconTextureAtlases>
</GameData>