<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Created by ModBuddy on 2/10/2023 10:08:02 AM -->
<GameData>
	<Language_en_US>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_ADJECTIVE">
			<Text>Ukrainian</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DESC">
			<Text>Ukrainian Empire</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_DAWN_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT">
			<Text>Slava Ukraini, courageous Volodymyr Zelenskyy, president and staunch defender of Ukraine. A former comedian, life imitated art when you were elected president of Ukraine after playing a teacher-elected-president of Ukraine in your comedy, Servant of the People. But your real presidency was far more turbulent than your one on TV. After spending your first few years rooting out corruption, in 2022, Russia invaded your homeland, seeking to seize it for itself. You stood bravely against them, becoming an international icon for your steadfast resoluteness in defence of your homeland and people. You stayed in Kyiv as enemy forces sought your death. You led the military at Ukraine’s hour of greatest need. You appealed to the international community for aid, being incredibly successful in doing so, receiving military assistance to fight the aggressors while isolating Russia from the international community. It is a fight you are just in, and it is a fight that you shall win.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]Oh fearless Volodymyr Zelenskyy, you must continue to stand against the naked aggression from your enemies. You must seek help of those willing to ensure the territorial and cultural integrity of Ukraine. Can you strengthen your alliances to help protect your people? Will you build a civilization that can stand the test of time?</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_SHORT_DESC">
			<Text>Ukraine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_1">
			<Text>History</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_1">
			<Text>Ukraine is a country in Eastern Europe. It is the second-largest European country after Russia, which it borders to the east and northeast. During the Middle Ages, Ukraine was the site of early Slavic expansion and the area later became a key centre of East Slavic culture under the state of Kyivan Rus', which emerged in the 9th century. The area was then contested, divided, and ruled by a variety of external powers for the next 600 years, including the Polish–Lithuanian Commonwealth, the Austrian Empire, the Ottoman Empire, and the Tsardom of Russia. Ukrainian nationalism developed, and following the Russian Revolution in 1917, the short-lived Ukrainian People's Republic was formed. The Bolsheviks consolidated control over much of the former empire and established the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic. Ukraine gained independence in 1991 as the Soviet Union dissolved, and declared itself neutral. A series of mass demonstrations, known as the Euromaidan, led to the establishment of a new government in 2014 after a revolution. Russia then unilaterally annexed Ukraine's Crimean Peninsula; and pro-Russian unrest culminated in a war between Russian-backed separatists and government forces in eastern Ukraine. Russia later launched a full-scale invasion of Ukraine in February 2022.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_2">
			<Text>Cultural Footprints</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_2">
			<Text>Settlement by modern humans in Ukraine and its vicinity dates back to 32,000 BC, with evidence of the Gravettian culture in the Crimean Mountains. By 4,500 BC, the Neolithic Cucuteni-Trypillia culture was flourishing in wide areas of modern Ukraine. Early Indo-European migrations from the Pontic steppes in the 3rd millennium BC spread Yamnaya Steppe pastoralist ancestry and Indo-European languages across large parts of Europe. During the Iron Age, the land was inhabited by Iranian-speaking Cimmerians, Scythians, and Sarmatians. From the 6th century BC, Greek, Roman, and Byzantine colonies were established on the north-eastern shore of the Black Sea, such as at Tyras, Olbia, and Chersonesus. These thrived into the 6th century AD. The Goths stayed in the area, but came under the sway of the Huns from the 370s. In the 5th and 6th centuries, the Early Slavic, Antes people lived in Ukraine. The Antes were the ancestors of Ukrainians: White Croats, Severians, Eastern Polans, Drevlyans, Dulebes, Ulichians, and Tiverians. In the 7th century, the territory that is now eastern Ukraine was the centre of Old Great Bulgaria. At the end of the century, the majority of Bulgar tribes migrated in different directions, and the Khazars took over much of the land.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_3">
			<Text>Golden Kyiv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_3">
			<Text>The establishment of the state of Kyivan Rus' remains obscure and uncertain. The state included much of present-day Ukraine, Belarus and the western part of European Russia. According to the Primary Chronicle, the Rus' people initially consisted of Varangians from Scandinavia. In 882, the pagan Prince Oleg conquered Kyiv from Askold and Dir and proclaimed it as the new capital of the Rus'. Anti-Normanist historians however argue that the East Slavic tribes along the southern parts of the Dnieper River were already in the process of forming a state independently. During the 10th and 11th centuries, Kyivan Rus' became the largest and most powerful state in Europe, a period known as its Golden Age. It began with the reign of Vladimir the Great, who introduced Christianity. During the reign of his son, Yaroslav the Wise, Kyivan Rus' reached the zenith of its cultural development and military power. The state soon fragmented as the relative importance of regional powers rose again. Kyivan Rus' finally disintegrated into separate principalities following Mstislav's death, though ownership of Kyiv would still carry great prestige for decades. The Mongol invasions in the mid-13th century devastated Kyivan Rus' and Kyiv was completely destroyed in 1240. Daniel of Galicia, son of Roman the Great, re-united much of south-western Rus', including Volhynia, Galicia, as well as Kyiv.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_4">
			<Text>The Years of Foreign Domination</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_4">
			<Text>In 1349, in the aftermath of the Galicia–Volhynia Wars, the area was partitioned between the Kingdom of Poland and the Grand Duchy of Lithuania. From the mid-13th century to the late 1400s, the Republic of Genoa founded numerous colonies in the Black Sea region of modern Ukraine and transformed these into large commercial centres headed by the consul, a representative of the Republic. In 1349, in the aftermath of the Galicia–Volhynia Wars, the area was partitioned between the Kingdom of Poland and the Grand Duchy of Lithuania. From the mid-13th century to the late 1400s, the Republic of Genoa founded numerous colonies in the Black Sea region of modern Ukraine and transformed these into large commercial centres headed by the consul, a representative of the Republic. In 1569, the Union of Lublin established the Polish–Lithuanian Commonwealth, and most of the Ukrainian lands were transferred from Lithuania to the Crown of the Kingdom of Poland, becoming de jure Polish territory.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_5">
			<Text>Enter the Zaporozhian Host</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_5">
			<Text>Deprived of native protectors among the Ruthenian nobility, the peasants and townspeople began turning for protection to the emerging Zaporozhian Cossacks. In the mid-17th century, a Cossack military quasi-state, the Zaporozhian Host, was formed by Dnieper Cossacks and Ruthenian peasants. Poland exercised little real control over this population, but found the Cossacks to be useful against the Turks and Tatars, and at times the two were allies in military campaigns. In 1648, Bohdan Khmelnytsky led the largest of the Cossack uprisings against the Commonwealth and the Polish king, which enjoyed wide support from the local population. Khmelnytsky founded the Cossack Hetmanate. After Khmelnytsky suffered a crushing defeat at the Battle of Berestechko in 1651, he turned to the Russian tsar for help. In 1654, Khmelnytsky was subject to the Pereiaslav Agreement, forming a military and political alliance with Russia that acknowledged loyalty to the Russian monarch. After his death, the Hetmanate went through a devastating 30-year war amongst Russia, Poland, the Crimean Khanate, the Ottoman Empire, and Cossacks, known as "The Ruin". An attempt to reverse the decline was undertaken by Cossack Hetman Ivan Mazepa, who ultimately defected to the Swedes in the Great Northern War in a bid to get rid of Russian dependence, but they were crushed in the Battle of Poltava. In the years 1764–1781, Catherine the Great incorporated much of Central Ukraine into the Russian Empire, abolishing the Cossack Hetmanate and the Zaporozhian Sich.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_6">
			<Text>Growing Nationalism</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_6">
			<Text>After the annexation of Crimea by Russia in 1783, the newly acquired lands, now called Novorossiya, were opened up to settlement by Russians. The tsarist autocracy established a policy of Russification, suppressing the use of the Ukrainian language and curtailing the Ukrainian national identity. The 19th century saw the rise of Ukrainian nationalism. With growing urbanization and modernization and a cultural trend toward romantic nationalism, the Ukrainian intelligentsia committed to national rebirth and social justice emerged. The serf-turned-national-poet Taras Shevchenko and political theorist Mykhailo Drahomanov led the growing nationalist movement. Ukraine joined the Industrial Revolution later than most of Western Europe due to the maintenance of serfdom until 1861. Ukraine plunged into turmoil with the beginning of World War I, and fighting on Ukrainian soil persisted until late 1921. Initially, the Ukrainians were split between Austria-Hungary, fighting for the Central Powers, though the vast majority served in the Imperial Russian Army, which was part of the Triple Entente, under Russia.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_7">
			<Text>The New Ukrainian State</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_7">
			<Text>As the Russian Empire collapsed, the conflict evolved into the Ukrainian War of Independence, with Ukrainians fighting alongside, or against, the Red, White, Black and Green armies, with the Poles, Hungarians, and Germans also intervening at various times. An attempt to create an independent state, the left-leaning Ukrainian People's Republic was first announced by Mykhailo Hrushevsky, but the period was plagued by an extremely unstable political and military environment. It was first deposed in a coup d'état led by Pavlo Skoropadskyi, which yielded the Ukrainian State under the German protectorate, and the attempt to restore the UNR under the Directorate ultimately failed as the Ukrainian army was regularly overrun by other forces. The short-lived West Ukrainian People's Republic and Hutsul Republic also failed to join the rest of Ukraine. The result of the conflict was a partial victory for the Second Polish Republic, which annexed the Western Ukrainian provinces, as well as a larger-scale victory for the pro-Soviet forces, which succeeded in dislodging the remaining factions and eventually established the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic. The conflict over Ukraine, a part of the broader Russian Civil War, devastated the whole of the former Russian Empire, including eastern and central Ukraine. The fighting left over 1.5 million people dead and hundreds of thousands homeless in the former Russian Empire's territory. The eastern provinces were additionally impacted by a famine in 1921.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_8">
			<Text>Soviet Ukraine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_8">
			<Text>An underground Ukrainian nationalist and militant movement arose in the 1920s and 1930s, which gradually transformed into the Ukrainian Military Organization and later the Organisation of Ukrainian Nationalists. Meanwhile, the recently constituted Soviet Ukraine became one of the founding republics of the Soviet Union. During the 1920s, under the Ukrainisation policy pursued by the national Communist leadership of Mykola Skrypnyk, Soviet leadership at first encouraged a national renaissance in Ukrainian culture and language. Ukrainisation was part of the Soviet-wide policy of Korenisation, which was intended to promote the advancement of native peoples, their language and culture into the governance of their respective republics. These policies attracted many prominent former UNR figures, including former UNR leader Hrushevsky, to return to Soviet Ukraine, where they were accepted, and participated in the advancement of Ukrainian science and culture. This period was cut short when Joseph Stalin became the leader of the USSR following Lenin's death. The Ukrainian peasantry suffered from the programme of collectivization of agricultural crops. As members of the collective farms were sometimes not allowed to receive any grain until unrealistic quotas were met, millions starved to death in a famine known as the Holodomor or the "Great Famine", which was recognized by some countries as an act of genocide perpetrated by Joseph Stalin and other Soviet notables. Following on the Russian Civil War, and collectivisation, the Great Purge, while killing Stalin's perceived political enemies, resulted in a profound loss of a new generation of Ukrainian intelligentsia, known today as the Executed Renaissance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_9">
			<Text>National Suffering</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_9">
			<Text>German armies invaded the Soviet Union on 22 June 1941, initiating nearly four years of total war. The Axis initially advanced against desperate but unsuccessful efforts of the Red Army. In the battle of Kyiv, the city was acclaimed as a "Hero City", because of its fierce resistance. Although the majority of Ukrainians fought in or alongside the Red Army and Soviet resistance, in Western Ukraine an independent Ukrainian Insurgent Army movement arose, the UPA. It was created as the armed forces of the underground Organization of Ukrainian Nationalists, OUN. Both organizations, the OUN and the UPA, supported the goal of an independent Ukrainian state on the territory with a Ukrainian ethnic majority. Although this brought conflict with Nazi Germany, at times the Melnyk wing of the OUN allied with the Nazi forces. From mid-1943 until the end of the war, the UPA carried out massacres of ethnic Poles in the Volhynia and Eastern Galicia regions, killing around 100,000 Polish civilians, which brought reprisals. The republic was heavily damaged by the war, and it required significant efforts to recover. More than 700 cities and towns and 28,000 villages were destroyed. The situation was worsened by a famine in 1946–1947, which was caused by a drought and the wartime destruction of infrastructure, killing at least tens of thousands of people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_10">
			<Text>Road to Independence</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_10">
			<Text>In 1945, the Ukrainian SSR became one of the founding members of the United Nations, part of a special agreement at the Yalta Conference, and, alongside Belarus, had voting rights in the UN even though they were not independent. Following the death of Stalin in 1953, Nikita Khrushchev became the new leader of the USSR, who began the policies of De-Stalinization and the Khrushchev Thaw. During his term as head of the Soviet Union, Crimea was transferred from the Russian SFSR to the Ukrainian SSR, formally as a friendship gift to Ukraine and for economic reasons. By 1950, the republic had fully surpassed pre-war levels of industry and production. The Soviet government invested in hydroelectric and nuclear power projects to cater to the energy demand that the development carried. On 26 April 1986, however, a reactor in the Chernobyl Nuclear Power Plant exploded, resulting in the Chernobyl disaster, the worst nuclear reactor accident in history. The democratization of the Soviet Union fuelled nationalist and separatist tendencies among the ethnic minorities, including Ukrainians. As part of the so-called parade of sovereignties, on 16 July 1990, the newly elected Supreme Soviet of the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic adopted the Declaration of State Sovereignty of Ukraine. Outright independence was proclaimed on 24 August 1991 and approved by 92% of the Ukrainian electorate in a referendum on 1 December.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_11">
			<Text>Finding the Way of Ukraine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_11">
			<Text>Ukraine's new President, Leonid Kravchuk, went on to sign the Belavezha Accords and made Ukraine a founding member of the much looser Commonwealth of Independent States, though Ukraine never became a full member of the latter as it did not ratify the agreement founding CIS. Ukraine was initially viewed as having favourable economic conditions in comparison to the other regions of the Soviet Union, though it was one of the poorer Soviet republics by the end of the Soviet Union. However, during its transition to the market economy, the country experienced deeper economic slowdown than almost all of the other former Soviet Republics. The legacy of the economic policies of the nineties was the mass privatization of state property that created a class of extremely powerful and rich individuals known as the oligarchs. The first two presidents, Kravchuk and Leonid Kuchma, tended to balance the competing visions of Ukraine, though Yushchenko and Yanukovych were generally pro-Western and pro-Russian, respectively.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_12">
			<Text>Breakaways</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_12">
			<Text>There were two major protests against Yanukovych: the Orange Revolution in 2004, when tens of thousands of people went in protest of election rigging in his favour and another one in the winter of 2013/2014, when more gathered on the Euromaidan to oppose Yanukovych's refusal to sign the European Union–Ukraine Association Agreement. By the end of the 2014 protests, he fled from Ukraine and was removed by the parliament in what is termed the Revolution of Dignity, but Russia refused to recognize the interim pro-Western government. Even though Russia had signed the so-called Budapest memorandum in 1994 that said that Ukraine was to hand over nuclear weapons in exchange of security guarantees and those of territorial integrity, it reacted violently to these developments and started a war against its western neighbour. In late February and early March 2014, it annexed Crimea using its Navy in Sevastopol as well as the so-called little green men; after this succeeded, it then launched a proxy war in the Donbas via the breakaway Donetsk People's Republic and Luhansk People's Republic.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_13">
			<Text>The Fight Against Domination</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIV5_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_13">
			<Text>The military conflict with Russia shifted the government's policy towards the West. Shortly after Yanukovych fled Ukraine, the country signed the EU association agreement in June 2014, and its citizens were granted visa-free travel to the European Union three years later. In January 2019, the Orthodox Church of Ukraine was recognized as independent of Moscow, which reversed the 1686 decision of the patriarch of Constantinople and dealt a further blow to Moscow's influence in Ukraine. Finally, amid a full-scale war with Russia, Ukraine was granted candidate status to the European Union on 23 June 2022, under President Volodymyr Zelenskyy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Leader-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY">
			<Text>Zelenskyy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_1">
			<Text>Overview</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_1">
			<Text>Volodymyr Oleksandrovych Zelenskyy is a Ukrainian politician who has served as the sixth president of Ukraine since 2019. Born to a Ukrainian Jewish family and a former comedian and actor, his administration faced an escalation of tensions with Russia in 2021, culminating in the launch of an ongoing full-scale Russian invasion in February 2022. Zelenskyy's strategy during the Russian military buildup was to calm the Ukrainian populace and assure the international community that Ukraine was not seeking to retaliate. After the start of the invasion, Zelenskyy declared martial law across Ukraine and a general mobilisation of the armed forces. His leadership during the crisis has won him widespread international praise, and he has been described as a symbol of the Ukrainian resistance. Zelenskyy was named the Time Person of the Year for 2022 and opinion polls in Ukraine have ranked him as Ukraine's greatest president.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_2">
			<Text>Drenched in History</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_2">
			<Text>Volodymyr Oleksandrovych Zelenskyy was born to Jewish parents on 25 January 1978 in Kryvyi Rih, then in the Ukrainian Soviet Socialist Republic. His father, Oleksandr Zelenskyy, is a professor and computer scientist and the head of the Department of Cybernetics and Computing Hardware at the Kryvyi Rih State University of Economics and Technology; his mother, Rymma Zelenska, used to work as an engineer. His grandfather, Semyon Ivanovych Zelenskyy served as an infantryman, reaching the rank of colonel in the Red Army during World War II; Semyon's father and three brothers were killed in the Holocaust. Before starting elementary school, Zelenskyy lived for four years in the Mongolian city of Erdenet, where his father worked. Zelenskyy grew up speaking Russian. At the age of 16 he passed the Test of English as a Foreign Language and received an education grant to study in Israel, but his father did not allow him to go. He later earned a law degree from the Kryvyi Rih Institute of Economics.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_3">
			<Text>Kvartal 95 and 1+1</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_3">
			<Text>At age 17, he joined his local team competing in the KVN comedy competition. He was soon invited to join the united Ukrainian team "Zaporizhia-Kryvyi Rih-Transit", which performed in the KVN's Major League, and eventually won in 1997. That same year, he created and headed the Kvartal 95 team, which later transformed into the comedy outfit Kvartal 95. From 1998 to 2003, Kvartal 95 performed in the Major League and the highest open Ukrainian league of KVN, and the team members spent a lot of time in Moscow and constantly toured around post-Soviet countries. In 2003, Kvartal 95 started producing TV shows for the Ukrainian TV channel 1+1, and in 2005, the team moved to fellow Ukrainian TV channel Inter. In 2008, he starred in the feature film Love in the Big City, and its sequel, Love in the Big City 2. Zelenskyy also played the leading role in the 2012 film 8 First Dates and in sequels which were produced in 2015 and 2016. He recorded the voice of Paddington Bear in the Ukrainian dubbing of Paddington and Paddington 2.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_4">
			<Text>Art and War</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_4">
			<Text>In August 2014, Zelenskyy spoke out against the intention of the Ukrainian Ministry of Culture to ban Russian artists from Ukraine. Since 2015, Ukraine has banned Russian artists and other Russian works of culture from entering Ukraine. In 2018, the romantic comedy Love in the Big City 2 starring Zelenskyy was banned in Ukraine. In 2015, Zelenskyy became the star of the television series Servant of the People, where he played the role of the president of Ukraine. In the series, Zelenskyy's character was a high-school history teacher in his 30s who won the presidential election after a viral video showed him ranting against government corruption in Ukraine. There was absolutely no foreshadowing in this at all.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_5">
			<Text>The Servant of the People</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_5">
			<Text>In March 2018, members of Zelenskyy's production company Kvartal 95 registered a new political party called Servant of the People, the same name as the hit TV program Zelenskyy had starred in over the previous three years. Although Zelenskyy denied any immediate plans to enter politics and said he had registered the party name only to prevent it being appropriated by others, there was widespread speculation that he was planning to run. As early as October 2018, three months before his campaign announcement and six months before the presidential election, he was already a frontrunner in opinion polls. On 31 December, less than four months from the election, Zelenskyy announced his candidacy for president of Ukraine on the New Year's Eve evening show on the TV channel 1+1. His announcement up-staged the New Year's Eve address of incumbent president Petro Poroshenko on the same channel, which Zelenskyy said was unintentional and attributed to a technical glitch. Zelenskyy's presidential campaign against Poroshenko was almost entirely virtual. He did not release a detailed policy platform and his engagement with mainstream media was minimal, as he instead reached out to the electorate via social media channels and YouTube clips. In place of traditional campaign rallies, he conducted stand-up comedy routines across Ukraine with his production company Kvartal 95. He styled himself as an anti-establishment, anti-corruption figure, although he was not generally described as a populist.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_6">
			<Text>The Campaign Trail</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_6">
			<Text>Prior to the elections, Zelenskyy presented a team that included former finance minister Oleksandr Danylyuk and others. During the campaign, concerns were raised over his links to the oligarch Ihor Kolomoyskyi. The Israeli-Cypriot billionaire businessman had gained control of the 1+1 Media Group in 2010. President Poroshenko and his supporters claimed that Zelenskyy's victory would benefit Russia. On 19 April 2019 at Olimpiyskiy National Sports Complex presidential debates were held in the form of a show. In his introductory speech, Zelenskyy acknowledged that in 2014 he voted for Poroshenko. Although Zelenskyy initially said he would only serve a single term, he walked back this promise in May 2021, saying he had not yet made up his mind. Zelenskyy clearly won the first round of elections on 31 March 2019. In the second round, on 21 April 2019, he received 73 per cent of the vote to Poroshenko's 25 per cent, and was elected President of Ukraine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_7">
			<Text>His Excellency, the President of Ukraine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_7">
			<Text>Zelenskyy was inaugurated on 20 May 2019. Zelenskyy is the first Jewish president; with Volodymyr Groysman as prime minister, Ukraine became the first country other than Israel to simultaneously have a Jewish head of state and head of government. In his inaugural address, Zelenskyy dissolved the then Ukrainian parliament and called for early parliamentary elections. On 28 May, Zelenskyy restored the Ukrainian citizenship of Mikheil Saakashvili. Zelenskyy's first major proposal to change the electoral system from a plurality voting system to proportional representation with closed party lists was strongly rejected by the Ukrainian parliament, due to the belief that closed lists would lead to more corruption in government. In addition, on 6 June, lawmakers refused to include Zelenskyy's key initiative on reintroducing criminal liability for illegal enrichment in the parliament's agenda, and instead included a similar bill proposed by a group of deputies. Lawmakers, diplomats and judges were stripped of legal immunity on 3 September. In June 2021, Zelenskyy submitted to the Verkhovna Rada a bill creating a public registry of Ukraine's oligarchs, banning them from participating in privatizations of state-owned companies, and forbidding them from contributing financially to politicians. The bill was passed into law in September 2021.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_8">
			<Text>Conflict in the Donbas</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_8">
			<Text>One of Zelenskyy's central campaign promises had been to end the Russo-Ukrainian War and resolve the Russia-sponsored separatist movement there. On 3 June, Zelenskyy appointed former president Leonid Kuchma as Ukraine's representative in the Tripartite Contact Group for a settlement in the conflict. In October 2019, Zelenskyy announced a preliminary deal struck with the separatists, under which the Ukrainian government would respect elections held in the region in exchange for Russia withdrawing its unmarked troops. The deal was met with heavy criticism and protests by both politicians and the Ukrainian public. The agreement failed to ease the conflict, as the separatists continued their attacks and Russia continued providing them with weapons and ammunition. In December 2019, Russia and Ukraine agreed to resume talks mediated by France and Germany under the so-called Normandy Format, which had been abandoned in 2016; it was Zelenskyy's first face-to-face meeting with Vladimir Putin. In July 2020, Zelenskyy announced a formal ceasefire with the separatists.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_9">
			<Text>Prelude to War</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_9">
			<Text>In April 2021, in response to Russian military build-up at the Ukrainian borders, Zelenskyy spoke to American president Joe Biden and urged NATO members to speed up Ukraine's request for membership. On 26 November 2021, Zelenskyy accused Russia and Ukrainian oligarch Rinat Akhmetov of backing a plan to overthrow his government. In December 2021, Zelenskyy called for preemptive action against Russia. On 19 February, as worries of a Russian invasion of Ukraine grew, Zelenskyy warned the Munich Security Conference that Western nations should abandon their "appeasement" attitude toward Moscow. In the early hours of 24 February, shortly before the start of the Russian invasion, Zelenskyy recorded an address to the citizens of both Ukraine and Russia. He disputed claims of the Russian government about the presence of neo-Nazis in the Ukrainian government and stated that he had no intention of attacking the Donbas region, while highlighting his personal connections to the area.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_10">
			<Text>The Defence of the Homeland</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_10">
			<Text>On the morning of 24 February, Putin announced that Russia was initiating a "special military operation" in the Donbas. Russian missiles struck a number of military targets in Ukraine, and Zelenskyy declared martial law. Zelenskyy also announced that diplomatic relations with Russia were being severed, effective immediately. Later in the day, he announced general mobilisation. Staying in Kyiv despite being identified as Russia's top target, Zelenskyy watched as, in the early hours of 26 February, Russian troops conducted their most significant assault on the capital of Kyiv. More than 90% of Ukrainians supported the actions of Zelenskyy, including more than 90% in western and central Ukraine and more than 80% in Russian-speaking regions in eastern and southern Ukraine. During the invasion, Zelenskyy has been reportedly the target of more than a dozen assassination attempts; three were prevented due to tips from Russian FSB employees who opposed the invasion. Two of those attempts were carried out by the Wagner Group, a Russian paramilitary force, and the third by the Kadyrovites, the personal guard of Chechen leader Ramzan Kadyrov.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_11">
			<Text>Important International Relations</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_11">
			<Text>On 7 March 2022, as a condition for ending the invasion, the Kremlin demanded Ukraine's neutrality; recognition of Crimea, which had been annexed by Russia, as Russian territory; and recognition of the self-proclaimed separatist republics of Donetsk and Luhansk as independent states. On 8 March, Zelenskyy expressed willingness to discuss Putin's demands. He proposed a new collective security agreement for Ukraine with the United States, Turkey, France, Germany as an alternative to the country joining NATO. Zelenskyy's Servant of the People party said that Ukraine would not give up its claims on Crimea, Donetsk and Luhansk. Zelenskyy has made an effort to rally the governments of Western nations in an effort to isolate Russia. He has made numerous addresses to the legislatures of Western nations. In April 2022, Zelenskyy criticized Germany's ties with Russia. In May 2022, Zelenskyy said that Ukrainian men of conscription age had a duty to remain in Ukraine and that up to 100 Ukrainian soldiers were killed every day in the fighting in eastern Ukraine. Zelenskyy denounced suggestions by former US diplomat Henry Kissinger that Ukraine should cede control of Crimea and Donbas to Russia in exchange for peace. Throughout the war effort, Zelenskyy has stood as a symbol of Ukrainian resistance.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_HEADING_12">
			<Text>The Zelenskyy Family</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TEXT_12">
			<Text>In September 2003, Zelenskyy married Olena Kiyashko, with whom he had attended school and university. Kiyashko worked as a scriptwriter at Kvartal 95. The couple's first daughter, Oleksandra, was born in July 2004. Their son, Kyrylo, was born in January 2013. Zelenskyy's first language is Russian, and he is also fluent in Ukrainian and English. On 27 March 2022, Slovakia awarded Zelenskyy one of the country's top awards, the State Award of Alexander Dubček. Eduard Heger, the Slovak prime minister, compared the Russian invasion of Ukraine in 2022 to the Soviet invasion of Czechoslovakia in 1968. Ausichicrinites zelenskyyi, an extinct species of feather star described on 20 July 2022 by a group of Polish paleontologists, is named after Zelenskyy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_LIVED">
			<Text>Jan 25th, 1974 - ???? AD</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_NAME">
			<Text>Volodymyr Zelenskyy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_SUBTITLE">
			<Text>Leader of Ukraine</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CIVILOPEDIA_LEADERS_SAS_ZELENSKYY_TITLES_1">
			<Text>President</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Trait-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_SAS_ZELENSKYY_SHORT">
			<Text>Of Cossack Kin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_TRAIT_SAS_ZELENSKYY">
			<Text>While at war, receive a copy of every new Mounted, Armor, or Unique Unit built by a declared Friend, with XP based upon your [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism output. If at war with a larger foe, [ICON_CULTURE] Culture provides Production towards Siege units.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SAS_ZELENSKYY_UNITSPAWN">
			<Text>[COLOR_CYAN]A new unit has arrived from our allies. The righteous will join the righteous fight![ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Kilosh-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SAS_TDF">
			<Text>[COLOR_YELLOW]Territorial Defense Force[ENDCOLOR]</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SAS_TDF_HELP">
			<Text>A foreign batalltion of the Territorial Defence Force, able to move after attacking. Enemy units adjacent to a Territorial Defense Force receive a -10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength penalty.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SAS_TDF_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Unique Unit for Zelenskyy's Ukraine, able to move after attacking and costing less [ICON_PRODUCTION] to build than the Bazooka it replaces. Enemy units adjacent to a Territorial Defense Force receive a -10% [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength penalty.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_UNIT_SAS_TDF_TEXT">
			<Text>The Territorial Defence Forces are the military reserve component of the Armed Forces of Ukraine. The Territorial Defence Forces were formed after the reorganization of the Territorial Defence Battalions, volunteer militias created during the War in Donbas under the command of the Ministry of Defence. Territorial Defence units existed from 2015 until 2021 in semi-organized forms until 2022 when they were formally organized into a unified defense corps under the Territorial Defence Forces. It is formed by a core of part-time reservists, usually former combat veterans, and in cases of war can be expanded to local civilian volunteers for local defense. As a result of the 2022 Russian invasion of Ukraine, the Territorial Defense Forces reserves were activated and many civilians joined local Territorial Defense Forces groups to fight the Russian invaders. On 25 February, during the rapid Russian offensive into Kyiv, the Ukrainian government distributed 18,000 guns for people wishing to fight in Kyiv.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAS_TDF_PROMO">
			<Text>Welcome To Hell!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_SAS_TDF_PROMO_HELP">
			<Text>Reduces the [ICON_STRENGTH] Combat Strength of adjacent enemy units by -10%.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Kiva-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAS_TV_STATION">
			<Text>Television Station</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAS_TV_STATION_PEDIA">
			<Text>A television station is a set of equipment managed by a business, organisation or other entity, such as an amateur television operator, that transmits video content and audio content via radio waves directly from a transmitter on the earth's surface to any number of tuned receivers simultaneously. In Ukraine, commercial television is dominated by three major broadcasters: 1+1 media, StarLightMedia and Inter Media Group, which is the smallest Ukrainian major broadcaster. One of the main Ukrainian news channels, Channel 5, belongs to a former president of Ukraine, Petro Poroshenko. Volodymyr Zelenskyy announced his candidacy for president of Ukraine on the New Year's Eve evening show on the TV channel 1+1, after being a star for one of their biggest shows, Servant of the People. In 2022, as part of the war effort, Ukraine's TV outlets united. Dubbed the United News telemarathon, the country’s main channels broadcast the same content 24 hours a day, in order to cover the war effort, as many journalists left Kyiv. The International Forum 'Digital Broadcasting in Ukraine' is the annual event that takes place in Kyiv, Ukraine.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAS_TV_STATION_STRATEGY">
			<Text>Replacing the Broadcast Tower for Zelenskyy's Ukraine, the Television Station contains 2 slots for Great Works of Music instead of 1. If both Great Work slots are filled, the Television Station provides +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism per Military or Defensive building in its city and allows its city to heal damage faster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_BUILDING_SAS_TV_STATION_HELP">
			<Text>Replacing the Broadcast Tower for Zelenskyy's Ukraine, the Television Station contains 2 slots for Great Works of Music instead of 1. If both Great Work slots are filled, the Television Station provides +1 [ICON_CULTURE] Culture and +1 [ICON_TOURISM] Tourism per Military or Defensive building in its city and allows its city to heal damage faster.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!--Kiev Update-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_SAS_MINSK3">
			<Text>Minsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_SAS_MINSK3_ADJ">
			<Text>Minsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITYSTATE_SAS_MINSK3_PEDIA">
			<Text>Minsk is the capital and largest city of Belarus, situated on the Svislach and Nyamiha rivers. The earliest historical references to Minsk date to AD 1067, when it was noted as a provincial city within the principality of Polotsk. Since then, the city has often changed hands as part of Lithuania, Poland, the Russian Empire, and the USSR, often serving as the capital of its specific administrative region. During the first half of 1944, Minsk was the centre of German resistance to the Soviet advance and saw heavy fighting. Factories, municipal buildings, power stations, bridges, most roads and 80% of the houses were reduced to rubble. The city leveled, Minsk's population was reduced to a mere 50,000. [NEWLINE][NEWLINE]After World War II, Minsk was rebuilt, but not reconstructed. Throughout the 1990s, after the fall of communism, the city continued to change. As the capital of a newly independent country, Minsk quickly acquired the attributes of a major city and today Minsk stands as the major cultural centre of Belarus. The city represents a melting pot of Eastern European languages and cultures, housing numerous theatres, universities, and museums. It is home to the world famous Belarusian ballet and a symbol of the continued perseverance of the Belarusian people.</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Spy Names -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_9">
			<Text>Shaman</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_8">
			<Text>Kyrylo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_7">
			<Text>Denys</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_6">
			<Text>Redis</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_5">
			<Text>Oleksii</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_4">
			<Text>Valerii</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_3">
			<Text>Vitali</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_2">
			<Text>Yevhen</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_1">
			<Text>Ugolyok</Text>
			<Gender>feminine</Gender>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_SPY_NAME_CIV_SAS_ZELENSKYY_0">
			<Text>Witch</Text>
			<Gender>feminine</Gender>
		</Row>
		<!--City Names-->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_1">
			<Text>Kyiv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_2">
			<Text>Kharkiv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_3">
			<Text>Odesa</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_4">
			<Text>Dnipro</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_5">
			<Text>Mariupol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_6">
			<Text>Lviv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_7">
			<Text>Zaporizhzhia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_8">
			<Text>Chernihiv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_9">
			<Text>Mykolaiv</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_10">
			<Text>Kherson</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_11">
			<Text>Sumy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_12">
			<Text>Donetsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_13">
			<Text>Kryvyi Rih</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_14">
			<Text>Vinnytsia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_15">
			<Text>Bakhmut</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_16">
			<Text>Makiivka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_17">
			<Text>Luhansk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_18">
			<Text>Simferopol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_19">
			<Text>Poltava</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_20">
			<Text>Poltava</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_21">
			<Text>Khmelnytskyi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_22">
			<Text>Cherkasy</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_23">
			<Text>Chernivtsi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_24">
			<Text>Zhytomyr</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_25">
			<Text>Melitopol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_26">
			<Text>Rivne</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_27">
			<Text>Sevastopol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_28">
			<Text>Ivano-Frankivsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_29">
			<Text>Horlivka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_30">
			<Text>Ternopil</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_31">
			<Text>Kropyvnytskyi</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_32">
			<Text>Kremenchuk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_33">
			<Text>Lutsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_34">
			<Text>Bila Tserkva</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_35">
			<Text>Kramatorsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_36">
			<Text>Brovary</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_37">
			<Text>Uzhhorod</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_38">
			<Text>Berdiansk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_39">
			<Text>Nikopol</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_40">
			<Text>Sloviansk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_41">
			<Text>Severodonetsk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_42">
			<Text>Lysychansk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_43">
			<Text>Konotop</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_44">
			<Text>Uman'</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_45">
			<Text>Enerhodar</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_46">
			<Text>Hostomel</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_47">
			<Text>Izium</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_48">
			<Text>Irpin</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_49">
			<Text>Bucha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_50">
			<Text>Okhtyrka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_51">
			<Text>Volnovakha</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_52">
			<Text>Kamianske</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_53">
			<Text>Kupiansk</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_54">
			<Text>Pavlohrad</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_55">
			<Text>Mukachevo</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_56">
			<Text>Oleksandriia</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_57">
			<Text>Huliaipole</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_58">
			<Text>Chornobaivka</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_59">
			<Text>Bile</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_CITY_NAME_SAS_ZELENSKYY_60">
			<Text>Kerch</Text>
		</Row>
		<!-- Diplomacy Responses -->
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_FIRSTGREETING_1">
			<Text>Welcome to Ukraine. Right now the destiny of our country is being decided. The destiny of our people, whether Ukrainians will be free, whether they will be able to preserve their democracy.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DEFEATED_1">
			<Text>Tragedies are outpacing life. The tyranny is outpacing the democracy. But you will never devour our spirit. Slava Ukraini!</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DOW_GENERIC_1">
			<Text>The fight is here; I need ammunition, and you need a ride.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_ATTACKED_HOSTILE">
			<Text>The presence of your occupiers is a threat to the entire region and to global stability.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DEC_FRIENDSHIP_1">
			<Text>Without you, Ukraine is going to be lonely. We have proven our strengths, we have proven that as a minimum, we are exactly the same as you are. Join us.</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DENOUNCE_1">
			<Text>Think on your orders and the fulfilment of them. For these murders, for these tortures, for these arms torn off by explosions that lie on the streets. For shots in the backs of the heads of tied people.  This is how you will now be perceived. This is your image.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]([COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]They have publicly denounced us! NOTE: You are not at war.[ENDCOLOR])</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_DENOUNCE_FRIEND_1">
			<Text>Your tyranny has lost control over us. And it will never influence our minds again.[NEWLINE][NEWLINE]([COLOR_WARNING_TEXT]They have publicly denounced us! NOTE: You are not at war.[ENDCOLOR])</Text>
		</Row>
		<Row Tag="TXT_KEY_LEADER_SAS_ZELENSKYY_RESPONSE_TO_BEING_DENOUNCED_1">
			<Text>We, the world and history will take from you much more than you will ever take from Ukraine.</Text>
		</Row>
	</Language_en_US>
</GameData>